Sandhill	BISP
Crane	BISP
migration	O
#birdmigration	O
#Sandhillcranes	BISP
https://t.co/WFVPM7ghqF	LINK
new	O
species	O
online	O
:	O
Common	BISP
Redpoll	BISP
Acanthis	BISP
flamea	BISP
#birdmigration	O
#birdID	O
#vismig	O
#finch	BISP
#redpoll	BISP
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/U9qUuE05Dm	LINK
Fly	O
with	O
Greater	BISP
Spotted	BISP
Eagles	BISP
|	O
https://t.co/ttUIy6Prl6	LINK
|	O
#BirdMigration	O
https://t.co/aI8WgTbszf	LINK
Yellow	BISP
throaded	BISP
warbler	BISP
Setophaga	BISP
dominica	BISP
#warbler	BISP
#biodiversity	O
#birds	O
#birdmigration	O
...	O
https://t.co/mUR4WMUxtJ	LINK
new	O
species	O
online	O
:	O
Eurasian	BISP
Twite	BISP
:	O
https://t.co/k1SoCdLNBq	LINK
#birdmigration	O
#birdID	O
#birdIDguide	O
#ornithology	O
...	O
https://t.co/H2nYPCbgtY	LINK
RT	RTWT
@HenrikLerner	AUTH
:	O
Interesting	O
on	O
migration	O
routes	O
for	O
Greenland	LOC
White-fronted	BISP
Geese	BISP
#Ornithology	O
#goose	BISP
#birdmigration	O
https://t.co/p14GtAC…	LINK
The	O
#DownyWoodpecker	BISP
is	O
the	O
smallest	O
woodpecker	BISP
in	O
the	O
United	LOC
States	LOC
.	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/FKl4Qqblsc	LINK
https://t.co/RTJpPnSnTX	LINK
A	O
Ring-billed	BISP
Gull	BISP
poses	O
on	O
a	O
pylon	O
in	O
the	O
St	LOC
John	LOC
River	LOC
.	O
New	LOC
Brunswick	LOC
,	O
Canada	LOC
#Nikon	O
#D500	O
#photography	O
#birding	O
...	O
https://t.co/5oDjEQNRKu	LINK
RT	RTWT
@RIBirdHunter	AUTH
:	O
Invaders	O
from	O
the	O
north	O
!	O
Snow	BISP
Buntings	BISP
in	O
Providence	LOC
,	O
RI	LOC
,	O
Dec.	DATE
11	DATE
@RIAudubon	O
#birds	O
#NaturePhotography	O
https://t.co/I9Zek…	LINK
Tarabilla	BISP
europea	BISP
-LRB-	O
Saxicola	BISP
rubicola	BISP
-RRB-	O
.	O
Macho	O
.	O
Common	BISP
stonechat	BISP
.	O
Madrid	LOC
.	O
#best_birds_of_ig	O
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/CJPreYQU6S	LINK
Bird	O
Painting	O
Sparrow	BISP
Garden	O
Bird	O
https://t.co/SKQZpJccIl	LINK
via	O
@Etsy	O
#birds	O
#art	O
#painting	O
#gift	O
https://t.co/MBLVlVseuV	LINK
Lastly	O
...	O
Lunchtime	O
#Photography	O
#Birding	O
#BaldEagle	BISP
Pennypack	LOC
Park	LOC
on	O
the	O
#DelawareRiver	LOC
https://t.co/LQQsb53jJc	LINK
Home	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
really	O
nice	O
bird	O
in	O
the	O
backyard	O
.	O
This	O
Northern	BISP
Parula	BISP
is	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Caribbea	O
...	O
https://t.co/9ghBq6SqEp	LINK
Saying	O
hi	O
to	O
the	O
seagulls	BISP
#seagulls	BISP
#beach	O
#sea	O
#varadero	LOC
#cuba	LOC
#relaxing	O
#birds	O
en	O
Varadero	LOC
,	O
Cuba	LOC
https://t.co/2ve09xcmad	LINK
2017	DATE
December	DATE
19	DATE
1149	O
.	O
Burns	LOC
,	O
Oregon	LOC
.	O
Hawk	BISP
?	O
#Photography	O
#Birds	O
Fullsize	O
:	O
https://t.co/p08C0FavkC	LINK
https://t.co/nsAFRNDbhX	LINK
California	BISP
condor	BISP
update	O
-	O
nestling	O
#	O
871	O
appears	O
to	O
have	O
fledged	O
!	O
#ThomasFire	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/AYiLWrxi3P	LINK
Red	BISP
Tailed	BISP
Hawk	BISP
-	O
The	LOC
Coves	LOC
ESA	LOC
-	O
London	LOC
,	O
ON	O
??	O
#hawk	BISP
#birds	O
#wildlife	O
#wildlifephotography	O
#nature	O
...	O
https://t.co/YpuCPI867u	LINK
@patsplanet	O
Thank	O
you	O
,	O
Pat	PERS
!	O
American	BISP
Oystercatcher	BISP
near	O
the	O
Cafe	LOC
Fear	LOC
River	LOC
:	O
https://t.co/lVj783GB2e	LINK
...	O
#birds	O
#nature	O
MISSING	O
Bird	O
Cockatiel	BISP
from	O
BishopAuckland	LOC
County	LOC
Durham	LOC
https://t.co/6S7VeWe2u9	LINK
#bishopauckland	LOC
#	O
#bird	O
#petregister	O
pls	O
RT	O
RT	RTWT
@rbabox	AUTH
:	O
A	O
Red-throated	BISP
Pipit	BISP
has	O
just	O
been	O
confirmed	O
in	O
San	LOC
Diego	LOC
County	LOC
,	O
California	LOC
-LRB-	O
CODE	O
3	O
-RRB-	O
https://t.co/ODY2A1gg4m	LINK
#ABARare	O
#birding	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@rbabox	AUTH
:	O
A	O
White-collared	BISP
Seedeater	BISP
continues	O
in	O
Starr	LOC
County	LOC
,	O
Texas	LOC
https://t.co/2CmvRhKuF8	LINK
#ABARare	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/4M7W0HmWIJ	LINK
RT	RTWT
@rbabox	AUTH
:	O
A	O
Tufted	BISP
Duck	BISP
has	O
just	O
been	O
confirmed	O
in	O
Suffolk	LOC
County	LOC
,	O
New	LOC
York	LOC
-LRB-	O
CODE	O
3	O
-RRB-	O
https://t.co/FxkhUftkIe	LINK
#ABARare	O
#birding	O
https://t.…	LINK
RT	RTWT
@rbabox	AUTH
:	O
A	O
Garganey	BISP
continues	O
in	O
Santa	BISP
Barbara	BISP
County	BISP
,	O
California	BISP
!	O
https://t.co/HbHaPmyrnj	LINK
#ABARare	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/BDlporTsOE	LINK
Pelicans	BISP
in	O
San	LOC
Remo	LOC
,	O
Victoria	LOC
...	O
#pelican	BISP
#birds	O
@	O
San	LOC
Remo	LOC
,	O
Victoria	LOC
https://t.co/7ZxB4JKWQG	LINK
Bald	BISP
eagles	BISP
above	O
Odell	LOC
Lake	LOC
;	O
Oregon	LOC
Cascades	LOC
.	O
#birding	O
#baldeagles	BISP
https://t.co/LcSFlg6vYH	LINK
First	O
time	O
spotting	O
a	O
Firecrest	BISP
,	O
at	O
West	LOC
Pentire	LOC
today	TIME
.	O
#northcornwall	LOC
#pentire	O
#bird	O
#firecrest	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/1OXtiIhloI	LINK
Mrs	O
Bluebird	BISP
,	O
coming	O
home	O
...	O
#bluebird	BISP
#home	O
#nc	O
#beautifulnc	O
#bird	O
#winter	O
@	O
Durham	LOC
,	O
North	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/BZBRW1X2bB	LINK
``	O
Mine	O
?	O
''	O
#seagull	LOC
#gull	LOC
#pest	O
#bird	O
#pixar	O
#findingnemo	O
#beach	O
#lagunabeach	LOC
@	O
Laguna	LOC
Beach	LOC
,	O
...	O
https://t.co/1DwPpzkBuA	LINK
Snowy	BISP
egret	BISP
chilling	O
out	O
at	O
Lake	ORG
Apopka	ORG
Wildlife	ORG
Drive	ORG
12-25-17	DATE
.	O
#naturelovers	O
@NatGeo	ORG
@natgeowild	ORG
@NatGeoMag	ORG
...	O
https://t.co/Pc0KBEYpCl	LINK
Apologies	O
,	O
correction	O
to	O
that	O
last	O
post	O
:	O
Brants	BISP
spotted	BISP
-LRB-	O
not	O
Canada	BISP
Geese	BISP
-RRB-	O
...	O
#birding	O
w/o	O
a	O
field	O
guide	O
Snowy	BISP
Owl	BISP
in	O
New	LOC
Jersey	LOC
,	O
digiscoped	O
with	O
an	O
iPhone	O
8	O
Plus	O
&	O
a	O
Phone	O
Skope	O
through	O
a	O
Swarovski	O
ATX	O
65mm	O
scope	O
...	O
https://t.co/ELhSbgKSD8	LINK
Read	O
about	O
a	O
Virginia	O
birder	O
trying	O
to	O
save	O
birds	O
from	O
fatal	O
window	O
strikes	O
:	O
Crying	O
fowl	BISP
:	O
New	ORG
YMCA	ORG
threatens	O
birds	O
,	O
...	O
https://t.co/bTp81xHN5M	LINK
A	O
Northern	BISP
Waterthrush	BISP
forages	O
San	LOC
Diego	LOC
Creek	LOC
in	O
#Irvine	LOC
,	O
#OrangeCounty	LOC
,	O
#California	LOC
,	O
USA	LOC
.	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
#bird	O
...	O
https://t.co/V1ctAosHmZ	LINK
A	O
beautiful	O
Peacock	BISP
resting	O
uhhunder	O
some	O
trees	O
at	O
the	O
Honolulu	ORG
Zoo	ORG
.	O
November	DATE
2017	DATE
.	O
.	O
.	O
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/82rAMu0poO	LINK
It	O
's	O
a	O
banner	O
year	O
for	O
Snowy	BISP
Owls	BISP
in	O
northern	LOC
Michigan	LOC
.	O
https://t.co/WZ8vZorZwM	LINK
#owls	BISP
#birding	O
#Michigan	LOC
East	LOC
Coast	LOC
visit	O
from	O
a	O
Mountain	BISP
Bluebird	BISP
.	O
What	O
a	O
treat	O
!!	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/xuravoK2Uq	LINK
PHOEBE	BISP
'S	BISP
HERON	BISP
is	O
a	O
lovely	O
middle-grade	O
novel	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Rockies	LOC
in	O
the	O
year	O
1900	DATE
,	O
as	O
the	O
Audubon	ORG
Society	ORG
conservat	O
...	O
https://t.co/WyUjXR5dRM	LINK
Young	BISP
Costa	BISP
's	BISP
hummingbird	BISP
,	O
Arizona	LOC
.	O
#hummingbirds	BISP
#birds	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
#naturephotography	O
|	O
@field_archive	O
RT	O
...	O
https://t.co/y6cUE5Vog0	LINK
Swan	BISP
Lake	BISP
as	O
performed	O
by	O
trumpeter	BISP
swans	BISP
at	O
Riverlands	ORG
Migratory	ORG
Bird	ORG
Sanctuary	ORG
.	O
#Missouri	LOC
#Swans	BISP
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/qIZFPpMwop	LINK
Gila	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
on	O
Saguaro	LOC
Cactus	LOC
in	O
Chandler	LOC
,	O
AZ.	LOC
#gila	BISP
#woodpecker	BISP
#bird	O
#birds	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
#cactus	O
#desert	O
...	O
https://t.co/NqTIJpsAjJ	LINK
RT	RTWT
@grasstraximage	AUTH
:	O
Canada	BISP
Geese	BISP
taking	O
off	O
@rspbconwy	O
.	O
@Natures_Voice	O
@BirdWatchingMag	O
#wildlifephotography	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/JYcUmZ9zPD	LINK
RT	RTWT
@SwanLavenham	AUTH
:	O
Swans	BISP
flying	O
over	O
Suffolk	LOC
during	O
the	O
wintertime	O
#WinterWonderland	O
#Winter	O
#Swans	BISP
#Birds	O
#Suffolk	LOC
https://t.co/aMUQHVdW2S	LINK
RT	RTWT
@carolpopegordon	AUTH
:	O
Swan	BISP
Lake	BISP
as	O
performed	O
by	O
trumpeter	BISP
swans	BISP
at	O
Riverlands	ORG
Migratory	ORG
Bird	ORG
Sanctuary	ORG
.	ORG
#Missouri	ORG
#Swans	ORG
#birds	O
#wildlifepho	O
...	O
Back	O
yard	O
visitor	O
from	O
Christmas	TIME
week	TIME
,	O
'	O
16	O
,	O
SE	O
GA.	O
.	O
Young	O
male	SEX
rose-breasted	BISP
grosbeak	BISP
.	O
#birding	O
#birds	O
#bird	O
...	O
https://t.co/glymH1RF9x	LINK
A	O
mother	SEX
peacock	BISP
and	O
her	O
chicks	O
in	O
Kauai	LOC
,	O
Hawaii	LOC
.	O
https://t.co/TRG7O90bEs	LINK
#birds	O
RT	O
https://t.co/74nuS0pTng	LINK
RT	RTWT
@KkevVY	AUTH
:	O
East	LOC
Coast	LOC
visit	O
from	O
a	O
Mountain	BISP
Bluebird	BISP
.	O
What	O
a	O
treat	O
!!	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/xuravoK2Uq	LINK
https://t.co/XUS9xmKAAL	LINK
so	O
many	O
Seagulls	BISP
at	O
Marine	LOC
Drive	LOC
,	O
#mumbainews	O
#Mumbai	LOC
#migration	O
#birds	O
#BirdsUp	O
...	O
https://t.co/JymgZbiosx	LINK
RT	RTWT
@cheryl_dumoulin	AUTH
:	O
Red	BISP
Tailed	BISP
Hawk	BISP
-	O
The	LOC
Coves	LOC
ESA	LOC
-	O
London	LOC
,	O
ON	O
??	O
#hawk	O
#birds	O
#wildlife	O
#wildlifephotography	O
#nature	O
#NatureisAmazing	O
#	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@TheMaruruns	AUTH
:	O
White	BISP
Peafowl	BISP
at	O
#Bali	ORG
#Zoo	ORG
???????	O
Before	O
visiting	O
to	O
Bali	LOC
,	O
check	O
this	O
from	O
here	O
?	O
https://t.co/sbOr3Mo2WY	LINK
#bird	O
#animal	O
#	O
...	O
Very	O
cute	O
!	O
Peach-faced	BISP
Lovebird	BISP
in	O
Kofu	LOC
Syowa	LOC
shopping	O
mall	O
?????????	O
???????	O
in	O
??????????	O
#twinglish	O
#bird	O
#cute	O
https://t.co/QMRDPxDmQp	LINK
#Lost	O
Parakeet	BISP
#Bird	O
--	O
Wilton	LOC
Manors	LOC
/	O
Fort	LOC
Lauderdale	LOC
,	O
#FL	O
https://t.co/NlcrLrkp13	LINK
#LostBird	O
...	O
https://t.co/Ue0L1qXer5	LINK
An	O
India	LOC
trip	O
full	O
of	O
many	O
highlights	O
such	O
as	O
this	O
phone-scoped	O
Indian	BISP
Courser	BISP
,	O
stunning	O
Tigers	O
,	O
the	O
Taj	LOC
Mahal	LOC
and	O
...	O
https://t.co/2gpncVpMEp	LINK
Tufted	BISP
Duck	BISP
yesterday	O
at	O
Langford	LOC
Lakes	LOC
Wiltshire	LOC
beautiful	O
reflections	O
?	O
@southwiltswild	O
@wildlife_uk	O
@CPREWilts	O
...	O
https://t.co/diKLp0HTp9	LINK
Why	O
has	O
there	O
been	O
an	O
increase	O
in	O
relatively	O
low	O
quality	O
prey	O
for	O
Guillemot	BISP
chicks	O
on	O
Skomer	LOC
?	O
Find	O
out	O
on	O
...	O
https://t.co/ltbxq7rGNH	LINK
Eurasian	BISP
tree	BISP
sparrow	BISP
hanging	O
out	O
with	O
friends	O
in	O
#Japan	LOC
.	O
Things	O
#magpies	O
see	O
when	O
on	O
holidays	O
in	O
Japan	LOC
.	O
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/p8MWrl6dqX	LINK
RT	RTWT
@Birdingcrtours	AUTH
:	O
Taiwanese	BISP
barbet	BISP
during	O
our	O
Taiwan	LOC
#birding	O
tour	O
#birdwatching	O
#travelphotography	O
https://t.co/RKLSMEHvGC	LINK
Ok	O
#connecticut	O
,	O
who	O
's	O
banded	O
Canada	BISP
goose	BISP
-LRB-	O
Branta	BISP
canadensis	BISP
-RRB-	O
is	O
this	O
?	O
@KRBurgio	O
@ConnDEEP	O
help	O
me	O
out	O
!	O
Seen	O
at	O
El	O
...	O
https://t.co/xfAgebnwLt	LINK
RT	RTWT
@ANS_Productions	AUTH
:	O
Canada	BISP
Goose	BISP
-	O
Rural	O
#landscape	O
-	O
Pembrokeshire	LOC
@ThePhotoHour	O
#ThePhotoHour	O
#photography	O
#bird	O
#geese	BISP
#goose	BISP
#wildlife	O
...	O
Puffin	BISP
-	O
May	DATE
2016	DATE
-	O
Iceland	LOC
?	O
#puffin	BISP
#puffins	BISP
#iceland	LOC
#mystopover	O
#niceland	O
#everydayiceland	O
#travel	O
#holidays	O
...	O
https://t.co/x2jHaAmrhu	LINK
Is	O
this	O
a	O
red-bellied	BISP
woodpecker	BISP
?	O
Also	O
,	O
is	O
eastern	LOC
Massachusetts	LOC
in	O
its	O
range	O
?	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
at	O
the	O
feeder	O
this	O
morn	O
...	O
https://t.co/8sUtLkQl7i	LINK
From	O
@IBIS_journal	O
2016	O
|	O
Non-breeding	BISP
Cackling	BISP
,	O
Ross	BISP
's	BISP
and	O
Snow	BISP
Geese	BISP
on	O
Baffin	LOC
Island	LOC
show	O
no	O
loss	O
of	O
body	O
mass	O
d	O
...	O
https://t.co/Mrmxjm2UN6	LINK
Endangered	O
Woodpecker	BISP
Nest	O
Monitoring	O
Project	O
at	O
Cedar	LOC
Creek	LOC
#prison	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/csytDeaabD	LINK
Bad	O
Hair	O
Day	O
#cardinal	BISP
#birds	O
@	O
Chokes	O
Place	O
https://t.co/JXG8qA3rMW	LINK
Here	O
's	O
some	O
colour	O
on	O
a	O
dark	O
and	O
cold	O
UK	LOC
winters	O
night	O
!	O
A	O
Crimson-backed	BISP
Tanager	BISP
phone-scoped	O
on	O
my	O
Colombia	LOC
trip	O
e	O
...	O
https://t.co/t3GDDUNzqx	LINK
A	O
baby	O
swan	BISP
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
photo	O
about	O
a	TIME
year	TIME
ago	TIME
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Adelaide	LOC
#cute	O
#cuteanimals	O
#animals	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/cMJlwnXx3O	LINK
Young	BISP
Costa	BISP
's	BISP
hummingbird	BISP
,	O
Arizona	LOC
.	O
#hummingbirds	BISP
#birds	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
#naturephotography	O
|	O
@field_archive	O
RT	O
...	O
https://t.co/BJvW4dBxtM	LINK
American	BISP
robin	BISP
on	O
a	O
very	O
cold	O
winter	O
day	O
in	O
New	LOC
Jersey	LOC
#robin	BISP
#bird	O
#birdsofinstagram	O
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/zWPqvCmOL5	LINK
Canada	BISP
geese	BISP
contorting	O
themselves	O
and	O
looking	O
all	O
kinds	O
of	O
goofy	O
while	O
spotting	O
their	O
landing	O
.	O
#birds	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/mjXfGUG4Fc	LINK
TURKEY	BISP
VULTURE	BISP
:	O
What	O
are	O
these	O
vultures	BISP
up	O
to	O
?	O
A	O
vulture	BISP
greeting	O
?	O
A	O
``	O
get	O
off	O
my	O
perch	BISP
tantrum	BISP
''	O
?	O
From	O
a	O
blind	O
at	O
P	O
...	O
https://t.co/4ZXV0mtHKI	LINK
birdwatching	O
:	O
Kolibri	BISP
-	O
Hummingbird	BISP
https://t.co/DJQGHcPwW4	LINK
#birding	O
Tamaulipas	BISP
Crow	BISP
in	O
Rockport	LOC
.	O
Great	O
photo	O
by	O
Pat	PERS
Wight	PERS
.	O
It	O
's	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
with	O
Whooping	BISP
Cranes	BISP
.	O
Hope	O
someone	O
gets	O
a	O
ph	O
...	O
https://t.co/qczrbJj2du	LINK
Good	O
morning	O
everyone	O
!	O
I	O
'm	O
enjoying	O
my	O
morning	O
view	O
now	O
??	O
#maxthecockatoo	O
#bird	O
#parrots	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/lYIlyuXTgr	LINK
Snowy	BISP
Owl	BISP
-LRB-	O
Bubo	BISP
scandiacus	BISP
-RRB-	O
,	O
White	O
Co.	O
,	O
Indiana	LOC
on	O
28	DATE
December	DATE
2017	DATE
.	O
#naturephotography	O
#nature	O
#biology	O
#birding	O
...	O
https://t.co/RWi8HieSxO	LINK
2017	DATE
Best	O
Photos	O
:	O
Golden	BISP
#eagle	BISP
vs.	O
#drone	O
during	O
military	O
exercise	O
in	O
SW	LOC
France	LOC
.	O
via	O
@reuterspictures	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/6fTo9tZaPp	LINK
Red	BISP
vented	BISP
bulbul	BISP
at	O
Sai	ORG
Vishram	ORG
Beach	ORG
Resort	ORG
,	O
Byndoor	LOC
#nature	O
#closetonature	O
#naturephotography	O
#naturelovers	O
...	O
https://t.co/dGZgnMRrQ2	LINK
Spotted	O
today	O
among	O
the	O
mistletoe	O
:	O
tufted	BISP
titmouse	BISP
and	O
Carolina	BISP
chickadee	BISP
.	O
#birds	O
#alabama	O
https://t.co/pGPViZMsSW	LINK
Close	O
up	O
on	O
a	O
male	SEX
Wood	BISP
Duck	BISP
in	O
breeding	O
plumage	O
,	O
found	O
at	O
LaSalle	LOC
Park	LOC
&	LOC
Marina	LOC
,	O
Burlington	LOC
,	O
Ontario	LOC
#BurlON	O
...	O
https://t.co/qPZm7l3YPF	LINK
RT	RTWT
https://t.co/RpqEHbcO0g	LINK
Snowy	BISP
Owl	BISP
-LRB-	O
Bubo	BISP
scandiacus	BISP
-RRB-	O
,	O
White	O
Co.	O
,	O
Indiana	O
on	O
28	O
December	O
2017	O
.	O
#naturephotography	O
...	O
https://t.co/OvuydZduE9	LINK
#LOST	O
COCKATIEL	BISP
#Bird	O
from	O
Mt	LOC
Warren	LOC
Park	LOC
#SouthLogan	LOC
https://t.co/ZYsfak1o5a	LINK
#Brisbane	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/GLSxl8GWqV	LINK
A	O
Buzzard	BISP
at	O
Hoe	LOC
in	O
Norfolk	LOC
on	O
Boxing	TIME
Day	TIME
.	O
@Photoshop	O
#photoshop	O
#bird	O
#buzzard	O
https://t.co/VsEKYHoKrg	LINK
Royal	BISP
Spoonbills	BISP
in	O
the	O
Moyne	LOC
River	LOC
,	O
Port	LOC
Fairy	LOC
25-Dec-2017	DATE
#birds	O
#WildOz	O
#SouthWestVictoria	LOC
https://t.co/Jah3jbpwOn	LINK
Immune	O
condition	O
and	O
blood	O
parasites	O
in	O
three	NUMB
sparrow	BISP
species	O
with	O
different	O
migratory	O
status	O
in	O
central	LOC
Mexico	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/HqkWqNXTWl	LINK
Blood	O
concentrations	O
of	O
p	O
,	O
p	O
?	O
-	O
DDE	O
and	O
PCBs	O
in	O
Montagu	BISP
's	BISP
Harriers	BISP
breeding	O
in	O
Spain	LOC
and	O
Pallid	BISP
Harriers	BISP
in	O
Kazakhstan	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/3uH1nhR0Q2	LINK
Mouse	O
predation	O
affects	O
breeding	O
success	O
of	O
burrow-nesting	O
petrels	BISP
at	O
sub-Antarctic	LOC
Marion	LOC
Island	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/VPU5EUNsET	LINK
Manipur	O
to	O
start	O
satellite	O
tracking	O
of	O
Amur	BISP
Falcons	BISP
https://t.co/8CbeZIxw1w	LINK
Assam	ORG
Tribune	ORG
#ornithology	O
20	NUMB
Hawfinch	BISP
still	O
at	O
Darley	LOC
Dale	LOC
at	O
St	LOC
Helen	LOC
's	LOC
in	O
yews	O
at	O
09.04	TIME
#derbyshire	O
#birding	O
Gadwall	BISP
landing	O
at	O
Langford	LOC
Lakes	LOC
last	TIME
week	TIME
#Gadwall	BISP
@southwiltswild	O
@wildlife_uk	O
@BirdingToday	O
@afternoonbirder	O
...	O
https://t.co/kVNDucSeHx	LINK
Enjoyed	O
opening	O
my	O
bedroom	O
curtains	O
to	O
find	O
this	O
Pied	BISP
Kingfisher	BISP
sat	O
right	O
outside	O
my	O
window	O
!	O
-LRB-	O
In	O
Uganda	LOC
,	O
not	O
North	O
...	O
https://t.co/VQ5e1DAmTJ	LINK
Glass	O
for	O
pencils	O
and	O
pens	O
with	O
Polar	BISP
owl	BISP
in	O
glasses	O
embroidery	O
design	O
Author	O
:	O
Maureen	PERS
Fresco	PERS
#polar	BISP
#owl	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/5wUxLh57Ir	LINK
#art	O
#drawing	O
#creative	O
RT	RTWT
@masillustra	AUTH
:	O
Bullfinches	BISP
in	O
red	O
and	O
#white	O
for	O
#colour_collective	O
these	O
last	TIME
days	TIME
of	TIME
20	TIME
...	O
https://t.co/MSGenUMfob	LINK
#robin	O
#garden	O
#bird	O
#friends	O
#wildlife	O
,	O
this	O
#robin	BISP
loves	O
to	O
fly	O
into	O
my	O
living	O
room	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
front	O
door	O
opens	O
.	O
.	O
...	O
https://t.co/jde6fhiNg7	LINK
There	O
's	O
a	O
summary	O
of	O
this	O
important	O
Curlew	BISP
habitat/predator	O
review	O
from	O
@_BTO	O
and	O
@RSPBScience	O
here	O
:	O
...	O
https://t.co/q9cINGcuLm	LINK
No	O
lifers	O
today	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
manage	O
to	O
spot	O
the	O
globally	O
endangered	O
Great	BISP
Knot	BISP
-LRB-	O
seen	O
here	O
between	O
two	O
Bar-tailed	BISP
Godwit	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/CVoXDxhmef	LINK
The	O
seemingly	O
ridiculous	O
name	O
of	O
Macaroni	BISP
Penguin	BISP
refers	O
to	O
their	O
fabulous	O
yellow	O
crests	O
which	O
reminded	O
early	O
natur	O
...	O
https://t.co/ZvGWF4JnEU	LINK
I	O
just	O
want	O
to	O
squeeeeezzze	O
these	O
little	O
guys	O
,	O
they	O
're	O
so	O
cute	O
!	O
????????	O
#eaglette	O
#eagles	BISP
#birding	O
...	O
https://t.co/VIz46xhPC9	LINK
Rare	O
sighting	O
of	O
the	O
elusive	O
timberdoodle	BISP
!	O
#birdwatching	O
#birds	O
#timberdoodle	BISP
#penguins	BISP
#newyork	LOC
#audubon	O
#winter	O
...	O
https://t.co/J3wQ9LNSm1	LINK
#birding	O
Cormorant	BISP
flying	O
over	O
Blashford	LOC
Lakes	LOC
#cormorant	BISP
#lake	O
#wildlife	O
#nature	O
#birding	O
@southwiltswild	O
@wildlife_uk	O
...	O
https://t.co/LgzUMmFT1f	LINK
The	O
Sandhill	BISP
Cranes	BISP
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
only	O
open	O
water	O
spaces	O
yesterday	TIME
in	O
this	O
crack	O
in	O
Kent	BISP
Lake	BISP
at	O
Kensington	BISP
Metr	O
...	O
https://t.co/dnbGAzrd9z	LINK
#BirdThePreserves	O
RT	RTWT
@chicagobotanic	AUTH
:	O
Take	O
a	O
winter	O
#birding	O
walk	O
to	O
try	O
to	O
find	O
cardinals	BISP
and	O
cedar	BISP
waxwings	BISP
as	O
we	O
...	O
https://t.co/6TniBfZwHk	LINK
Feeding	O
the	O
birds	O
on	O
another	O
subzero	O
morning	O
!	O
Birding	O
from	O
inside	O
today	O
!	O
#Chickadees	BISP
are	O
among	O
my	O
top	O
10	O
faves	O
.	O
...	O
https://t.co/VCRepLTZX4	LINK
#bird	O
#massage	O
#Vogel	O
https://t.co/F2ekXyWvfo	LINK
Such	O
a	O
cute	O
little	O
#bird	O
these	O
#longTailedTit	BISP
?	O
https://t.co/epKy5wKclY	LINK
My	O
more	O
artistic	O
better	O
half	O
@mariibiichos	O
has	O
drawn	O
the	O
yellow-headed	BISP
picathartes	BISP
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
most	O
wanted	O
world	O
bir	O
...	O
https://t.co/GhvVlZ4AVd	LINK
Common	BISP
Kingfisher	BISP
#sony	O
A77ii	O
Sony	O
70-400	O
#saudi_birds	O
#bird	O
...	O
https://t.co/Hnb2tsl4T0	LINK
And	O
secondly	O
Scarlet-thighed	BISP
Dacnis	BISP
,	O
a	O
bit	O
more	O
difficult	O
to	O
phone-scope	O
as	O
it	O
moved	O
through	O
the	O
canopy	O
but	O
worth	O
...	O
https://t.co/fuFE2u1Flb	LINK
#birds	O
#parrots	BISP
#toucan	BISP
#photography	O
https://t.co/iaiVLyskOe	LINK
Honeycreeper	BISP
adorableness	BISP
:	O
Maui	LOC
?	O
alauahio	O
has	O
rapidly	O
hopping	O
places	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
tiny	O
insects	O
to	O
eat	O
...	O
-LRB-	O
Paroreomyza	BISP
m	O
...	O
https://t.co/SQS14wfVXx	LINK
An	O
egret	BISP
looks	O
for	O
fish	O
on	O
the	O
gulf	O
side	O
of	O
Marathon	LOC
Key	LOC
.	O
It	O
's	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
trip	O
!	O
#egret	BISP
#bird	O
#birds	O
#wildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/mVFi9ddPI8	LINK
Lastly	O
,	O
Juvenile	O
#BaldEagle	BISP
in	O
flight	O
at	O
#BurlingtonIsland	LOC
#NJ	O
#Birding	O
Going	O
out	O
to	O
play	O
in	O
the	O
snow	O
.	O
L8tr	O
!	O
https://t.co/Sc2VPV9b0D	LINK
A	O
Black-headed	BISP
Gull	BISP
has	O
just	O
been	O
confirmed	O
in	O
Atlantic	LOC
County	LOC
,	O
NJ	LOC
-LRB-	O
CODE	O
3	O
-RRB-	O
https://t.co/6Roxupoa6O	LINK
#ABARare	O
...	O
https://t.co/k9FItGD0Tj	LINK
bird	O
watching	O
california	BISP
pigeons	BISP
black	O
birds	O
blue	O
bird	O
https://t.co/z2517uttkD	LINK
#birding	O
Female	SEX
Belted	BISP
Kingfisher	BISP
sp	O
.	O
Ceryle	BISP
alcyon	BISP
#your_best_birds	O
#bird	O
#birds	O
#birdsofinstagram	O
...	O
https://t.co/fnC9eX7fsN	LINK
#bird	O
#birds	O
#parrot	BISP
#parrots	BISP
#birdsofinstagram	O
#birding	O
#animal	O
#birdwatching	O
#loveit	O
...	O
https://t.co/1mFtcuLTbf	LINK
Sanderlings	BISP
in	O
flight	O
#sanderlings	BISP
#bird	O
#coastal	O
#RSPB	O
#rattrayhead	BISP
#aberdeenshire	BISP
#scotland	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/IlMPwzFTPk	LINK
I	O
had	O
to	O
pause	O
mid	O
yoga	O
session	O
yesterday	O
when	O
I	O
realised	O
a	O
starling	BISP
was	O
trapped	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
bird	O
feeders	O
...	O
https://t.co/FxTjDcyhJV	LINK
#bird	O
#pelican	BISP
#brown	O
#brownpelican	O
#shorebird	O
#florida	LOC
#sarasota	O
#dhackett	O
#wildlife	O
#audubon	O
...	O
https://t.co/OZzWSIcHLS	LINK
Yesterday	TIME
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bald	BISP
eagle	BISP
.	O
This	TIME
morning	TIME
,	O
a	O
trio	O
of	O
#osprey	BISP
went	O
skating	O
,	O
looking	O
for	O
fish	O
under	O
the	O
ice	O
,	O
no	O
do	O
...	O
https://t.co/3EXIQvpy8s	LINK
Red-tailed	BISP
hawk	BISP
in	O
the	O
snow	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
#birds	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/FbzKqzzFWv	LINK
#birding	O
?	O
Attitude	O
with	O
wings	O
.	O
Posted	O
by	O
@RichardMcLellan	O
Red-winged	BISP
Fairywren	BISP
-LRB-	O
Malurus	BISP
elegans	BISP
-RRB-	O
Walpole	LOC
Nornalup	LOC
National	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/f8vn73oqPj	LINK
Blue	BISP
heron	BISP
across	O
the	O
river	O
this	TIME
morning	TIME
.	O
Thru	O
the	O
65mm	O
scope	O
w/iPhone	O
6	O
.	O
#birding	O
#oregon	LOC
https://t.co/w7wzE72N9F	LINK
Miniature	O
acrylic	O
painting	O
of	O
a	O
Saffron	BISP
Toucanet	BISP
on	O
a	O
log	O
round	O
#art	O
#artwork	O
#painting	O
#acrylicpainting	O
#toucan	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/O6GdovZvsV	LINK
Check	O
out	O
#ACEO	O
Original	O
Acrylic	O
Pen	O
#Painting	O
Abstract	O
#Bird	O
Night	O
Wild	O
#Owl	BISP
ii	O
Sue	PERS
Flask	PERS
#Miniature	O
https://t.co/qFaB3HoFPv	LINK
via	O
@eBay	O
A	O
Partridge	BISP
in	O
a	O
Plum	O
Tree	O
.	O
#wood	O
#gold	O
#walnut	O
#stain	O
#frame	O
#art	O
#bird	O
#plum	O
#fruit	O
#bowl	O
#canvas	O
#fun	O
...	O
https://t.co/ossu6N48IH	LINK
Great	O
podcast	O
about	O
the	O
snowy	BISP
owls	BISP
irruption	O
with	O
@projsnowstorm	O
Scott	PERS
Weidensaul	PERS
,	O
always	O
very	O
interesting	O
.	O
...	O
https://t.co/os5vt6NQIq	LINK
Male	SEX
Scarlet	BISP
#Tanager	BISP
#Watch	O
#Bird	O
#Nature	O
#Photography	O
https://t.co/7Fhij5pewB	LINK
https://t.co/c2QZRDymYd	LINK
Many	O
of	O
my	O
Red	BISP
Tailed	BISP
Hawk	BISP
images	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
individual	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
her	O
Freyja	O
and	O
she	O
's	O
a	O
frequent	O
visitor	O
who	O
is	O
...	O
https://t.co/tUDa5Bg0Pl	LINK
The	O
White-breasted	BISP
Nuthatches	BISP
were	O
out	O
in	O
force	O
after	O
the	O
storm	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
hardly	O
seem	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
toss	O
about	O
the	O
ice	O
.	O
...	O
https://t.co/q2l2oLTcq0	LINK
My	O
summer	O
memories	O
.	O
.	O
from	O
bald	O
#BlueJays	BISP
to	O
splashing	O
#sparrows	BISP
.	O
.	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
po-pouri	O
of	O
#birds	O
around	O
our	O
home	O
.	O
.	O
enjoy	O
.	O
.	O
...	O
https://t.co/zJzj4hhjQ9	LINK
Parakeets	BISP
>	O
The	O
left-overs	O
.	O
10	NUMB
birds	O
that	O
did	O
n't	O
make	O
it	O
onto	O
the	O
b	O
-	O
>	O
https://t.co/0hdtHNU4wf	LINK
#bird	O
https://t.co/qjK8y4tBlA	LINK
I	O
can	O
not	O
figure	O
out	O
how	O
this	O
little	O
Sparrow	BISP
got	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
hiding	O
in	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
naming	O
h	O
...	O
https://t.co/VW7KpWGcvi	LINK
MISSING	O
Bird	O
Canary	BISP
from	O
Selby	LOC
North	LOC
Yorkshire	LOC
https://t.co/dOOfgfEela	LINK
#selby	O
#YO8	O
#bird	O
#petregister	O
pls	O
RT	O
``	O
Pool	O
Season	O
''	O
?	O
...	O
??	O
especie	O
:	O
Tenca	BISP
-LRB-	O
Mimus	BISP
Thenca	BISP
-RRB-	O
/	O
/	O
#tenca	BISP
#bird	O
#birdpool	O
#photo	O
...	O
https://t.co/Z7Tmwoj2LN	LINK
Female	SEX
Blackbird	BISP
posing	O
.	O
.	O
#blackbird	O
#bird	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
#wildlifephotography	O
#naturephotography	O
https://t.co/aSWLQKQwQe	LINK
#bird	O
#gull	BISP
#seagull	BISP
#beach	O
#ocean	O
#dhackett	O
#beach	O
#atlantic	O
#ameliaisland	O
#florida	LOC
#audubon	O
...	O
https://t.co/3DY6gjLsfd	LINK
#Snow	O
#birding	O
today	O
.	O
The	O
cold	O
ca	O
n't	O
stop	O
me	O
:	O
https://t.co/nZO0U7Vruv	LINK
#Birds	O
#Brooklyn	LOC
#Wildlife	O
#Winter	O
...	O
https://t.co/UacrRza6iq	LINK
Crow	BISP
in	O
Moonlight	O
Print	O
Bird	O
Reproduction	O
from	O
Original	O
Oil	O
https://t.co/IWAKkO12GE	LINK
#oilpainting	O
#prints	O
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/KVlMaKnzR1	LINK
``	O
Helmeted	BISP
Honeyeater	BISP
''	O
WIP	O
.	O
Ref	O
photo	O
by	O
CD	O
Photography	O
,	O
#PrismacolorPremier	O
Pencils	O
?	O
and	O
#FaberCastell	O
?	O
...	O
https://t.co/366Wz4xbn6	LINK
#bird	O
#birds	O
#sunbird	BISP
#birding	O
#birdphotography	O
#PhotographyIsArt	O
#SundayMorning	O
https://t.co/MXKYzpO6oq	LINK
You	O
've	O
never	O
seen	O
a	O
crow	BISP
do	O
this	O
!	O
#birds	O
#crows	BISP
#nature	O
#crowspitswater	O
https://t.co/tiXPrPgr7u	LINK
Closer	O
look	O
at	O
same	O
pied	BISP
cormorant	BISP
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
one	O
along	O
this	O
section	O
of	O
the	O
Cooks	LOC
River	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/ubzDVKtefz	LINK
Cardinal	BISP
on	O
the	O
go	O
#wildlife	O
#photography	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/N9HDsdDrUu	LINK
``	O
Stoic	O
Hunter	O
''	O
-	O
a	O
Red-Shouldered	BISP
Hawk	BISP
patiently	O
awaits	O
prey	O
-	O
https://t.co/YWkFdu2cep	LINK
#birds	O
#NaturePhotography	O
...	O
https://t.co/CGm76cHXFi	LINK
Hairy	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
and	O
Chickadee	BISP
eating	O
vegan	O
suet	O
#woodpecker	BISP
#chickadee	BISP
#birds	O
#ottawa	LOC
#chapelhill	O
...	O
https://t.co/XgiK2uhLdF	LINK
Robin	BISP
#art	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/X4tukhA0Ne	LINK
#birds	O
#Chickadee	BISP
#NaturePhotography	O
#ottawa	LOC
#dewberrytrail	O
https://t.co/uGadSmn0he	LINK
#hairywoodpecker	BISP
#woodpecker	BISP
#birds	O
#NaturePhotography	O
#ottawa	LOC
#ChapelHill	O
https://t.co/CvTEesfljV	LINK
#bird	O
#gull	BISP
#seagull	BISP
#beach	O
#ocean	O
#dhackett	O
#beach	O
#atlantic	O
#ameliaisland	O
#florida	LOC
#audubon	O
...	O
https://t.co/lMzMEwcYqU	LINK
#perruche	O
#parakeet	O
#budgie	O
#india	O
#tamilnadu	O
#bird	O
#pondicherry	O
https://t.co/q0V1CJqMV1	LINK
Beautiful	O
#pigeons	BISP
you	O
never	O
know	O
...	O
or	O
the	O
city	O
#rat	O
#bird	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
,	O
seeing	O
chnages	O
your	O
thoughts	O
https://t.co/Cps86w3hvw	LINK
#animals	O
#animal	O
#sheep	O
#owl	BISP
#elephant	O
#bird	O
#palmnutvulture	O
#wildlife	O
#nature	O
#instalife	O
...	O
https://t.co/kJk9q4b9BX	LINK
My	O
latest	O
trip	O
report	O
from	O
a	O
SOUTHERN	LOC
ECUADOR	LOC
tour	O
that	O
featured	O
Crescent-faced	BISP
Antpitta	BISP
and	O
Pale-headed	BISP
Brushfinch	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/DptfYX2Jur	LINK
The	O
resident	O
robin	BISP
has	O
been	O
enjoying	O
playing	O
around	O
in	O
the	O
snow	O
the	O
last	O
couple	O
of	O
days	O
.	O
#birding	O
#robin	BISP
#nature	O
https://t.co/JIRrfiqKKS	LINK
Black-shouldered	BISP
Kite	BISP
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tagus	LOC
Estuary	LOC
Natural	LOC
Reserve	LOC
,	O
near	O
Lisbon	LOC
last	O
month	O
#stunning	O
#birding	O
...	O
https://t.co/AOtBniu8j6	LINK
#bird	O
#eagle	BISP
#baldeagle	BISP
#american	O
#icon	O
#majestic	O
#florida	LOC
#usa	LOC
#symbol	O
#dhackett	O
#america	LOC
#americanicon	O
...	O
https://t.co/gySDq05HU6	LINK
And	O
this	O
is	O
precisely	O
why	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
#owls	BISP
at	O
#weddings	O
>	O
https://t.co/zTk6PjRuxC	LINK
#birds	O
#welfare	O
And	O
this	O
is	O
precisely	O
why	O
I	O
detest	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
#Owls	BISP
at	O
#weddings	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
fan	O
of	O
owls	BISP
do	O
n't	O
exploit	O
them	O
.	O
>	O
...	O
https://t.co/pwB6nIN3xT	LINK
Tree	BISP
Sparrow	BISP
sighting	O
in	O
Indiana	LOC
.	O
@USFWSMidwest	O
@audubonsociety	O
@bwdmag	O
@INFishWildlife	O
#birds	O
#birdwatching	O
...	O
https://t.co/ePs79mx2yH	LINK
Rainbows	BISP
and	O
robins	BISP
on	O
a	O
walk	O
round	O
Eastrington	LOC
.	O
#rainbow	BISP
#Robin	BISP
#walk	O
#hiking	O
#eastrington	LOC
#Yorkshire	LOC
#eastriding	O
...	O
https://t.co/hwdmwsadFU	LINK
2017	O
#ornithology	O
headlines	O
|	O
Geolocators	O
reveal	O
Connecticut	LOC
Warblers	BISP
'	O
amazing	O
oversea	O
migration	O
:	O
https://t.co/veoEF7cCpt	LINK
Inter-sexual	O
habitat	O
and	O
isotopic	O
niche	O
segregation	O
of	O
the	O
endangered	O
Monteiro	BISP
's	BISP
storm-petrel	BISP
during	O
breeding	O
...	O
https://t.co/U2NlsMj8y7	LINK
A	O
great	O
end	TIME
to	TIME
2017	TIME
with	O
the	O
possible	O
Heuglin	BISP
's	BISP
Gull	BISP
at	O
Buffalo	LOC
Creek	LOC
#Darwin	O
on	O
#NewYearsEve	TIME
.	O
Probable	O
that	O
this	O
i	O
...	O
https://t.co/x5wEwVtrLL	LINK
?????	O
?	O
Blue	BISP
Bird	BISP
on	O
the	O
road	O
https://t.co/juSEoMFuGZ	LINK
https://t.co/QXcpsWL9Xz	LINK
#Bird	O
Another	O
Lovely	O
tiny	O
spring	O
visitor	O
to	O
our	O
Forest	O
-	O
Black-Throated	BISP
Green	BISP
Warbler	BISP
#bird	O
#Nature	O
#photography	O
https://t.co/Yc1Dm9u24T	LINK
Happy	O
New	O
Year	O
!	O
Let	O
it	O
be	O
a	O
year	O
of	O
peace	O
,	O
love	O
and	O
freedom	O
#flickr	O
https://t.co/t9ZCuxDBy8	LINK
#robin	BISP
#birds	O
#photography	O
#nikon	O
Pelican	BISP
in	O
peace	O
!	O
Save	O
them	O
from	O
Eutrophication	O
!	O
#travelblog	O
#travelling	O
#Travelers	O
#backpacking	O
#Bangalore	O
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/srTRhZIXWO	LINK
PEEK-A-BOO	O
Photo	O
by	O
@avkashchevli	O
Spotted	O
Owlet	BISP
was	O
peeking	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
hole	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	NUMB
pair	NUMB
of	NUMB
an	O
owlet	BISP
,	O
but	O
...	O
https://t.co/4GxPmHnK0d	LINK
@seethelizards	O
Read	O
more	O
-	O
https://t.co/52hEDVWLed	LINK
#parrot	BISP
#pet	O
#bird	O
#macaw	BISP
#love	O
#color	O
#macawfcats	O
2017	O
#ornithology	O
headlines	O
|	O
New	O
manakin	BISP
described	O
from	O
northern	LOC
Peru	LOC
:	O
https://t.co/jYQ8tmxKY9	LINK
2017	DATE
#ornithology	O
headlines	O
|	O
Sandpiper	BISP
wanders	O
thousands	O
of	O
miles	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
sex	O
:	O
https://t.co/OH1PnRNJ2P	LINK
Another	O
misidenification	O
by	O
me	O
!	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
bad	O
at	O
#birding	O
so	O
far	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
Red-Bellied	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
.	O
Still	O
pretty	O
aw	O
...	O
https://t.co/0BY5kY210a	LINK
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
4	O
subspecies	O
of	O
the	O
spectacular	O
multi-colored	O
#paradisetanager	BISP
.	O
This	O
one	O
has	O
the	O
scarlet	O
rump	O
an	O
...	O
https://t.co/NbfQlND3f1	LINK
A	NUMB
pair	NUMB
of	NUMB
#ducks	BISP
asleep	O
at	O
@chatsworthhouse	O
#peakdistrict	O
buy	O
as	O
a	O
print	O
here	O
https://t.co/mF9ob7AQqR	LINK
#birding	O
#ad	O
...	O
https://t.co/WGn0junEGQ	LINK
Tufted	BISP
titmouse	BISP
#Backyardbirds	O
#birdwatching	O
#tuftedtitmouse	BISP
#birding	O
https://t.co/vlNBY8YsmA	LINK
Azure-winged	BISP
magpies	BISP
-LRB-	O
Cyanopica	BISP
cyana	BISP
-RRB-	O
Century	LOC
Park	LOC
,	O
Shanghai	LOC
,	O
China	LOC
.	O
#bird	O
#birding	O
#nature	O
...	O
https://t.co/XP2VykWdtY	LINK
#dove	BISP
#wild	O
#bird	O
https://t.co/BCiAmVRv5Q	LINK
Well	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
looking	O
for	O
snowy	BISP
#owls	BISP
and	O
did	O
n't	O
find	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
lucky	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
this	O
beautiful	O
short-eared	O
...	O
https://t.co/rbTAIHweBo	LINK
the	O
amazing	O
#murmuration	O
of	O
the	O
#Starling	O
in	O
#Aberystwyth	LOC
A	O
peregrine	BISP
turned	O
up	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
got	O
one	O
...	O
that	O
's	O
...	O
https://t.co/2GmXn32Vpd	LINK
Filled	O
the	O
bird	O
feeders	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
-LRB-	O
we	O
were	O
away	O
-RRB-	O
,	O
&	O
thought	O
for	O
sure	O
the	O
juncos	BISP
would	O
be	O
the	O
fir	O
...	O
https://t.co/TACjoweSdL	LINK
Blue	BISP
Jay	BISP
at	O
the	O
feeder	O
#birding	O
#wildlife	O
#opcmag	O
#natgeo	ORG
https://t.co/mAipzE59yN	LINK
Surf	BISP
Scoters	BISP
everywhere	O
!!!	O
**	O
Dream	O
Bird	O
**	O
Now	O
on	O
the	O
hunt	O
for	O
the	O
Gyr	BISP
-	O
the	O
ultimate	O
raptor	O
.	O
#Birding	O
Royal	BISP
spoonbill	BISP
#royalspoonbill	BISP
#ornithology	O
#birdsofaustralia	O
#birdsofsouthaustralia	O
#kangarooisland	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/oqmccCfEPm	LINK
Royal	BISP
spoonbill	BISP
#royalspoonbill	BISP
#ornithology	O
#birdsofaustralia	O
#kangarooisland	O
#birdsofinstagram	O
...	O
https://t.co/qukSssWfSw	LINK
The	O
fur	O
and	O
feather	O
family	O
members	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
#happynewyear	O
____	O
#kitty	O
#cat	O
#parakeet	BISP
#bird	O
...	O
https://t.co/H7oYAAdl3l	LINK
Last	O
#bird	O
sighting	O
of	O
2017	DATE
tweet	O
is	O
a	O
#Junco	BISP
spotted	O
Dec.	DATE
31	DATE
#WaterfrontTrail	O
#HamOnt	LOC
#Canada	LOC
#BirdPhotography	O
...	O
https://t.co/5QkWTq5Vcn	LINK
Juvenile	O
Grey	BISP
Butcherbird	BISP
-LRB-	O
Cracticus	BISP
torquatus	BISP
-RRB-	O
-	O
Walpole	LOC
Nornalup	LOC
National	LOC
Park	LOC
,	O
WA	LOC
.	O
#FindYourPark	O
@OurWAParks	O
...	O
https://t.co/CPjAWbpaAX	LINK
Peregrine	BISP
.	O
#peregrinefalcon	BISP
#falcon	BISP
#birding	O
#pnw	O
#epic	O
#nature	O
@	O
Skagit	LOC
River	LOC
https://t.co/yozLDMdmnY	LINK
You	O
guys	O
!	O
This	O
Barred	BISP
Owl	BISP
scared	O
the	O
S	O
**	O
T	O
out	O
of	O
me	O
today	O
.	O
Saw	O
him	O
near	O
Coos	LOC
Bay	LOC
Oregon	LOC
#birding	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
6	O
'	O
away	O
wh	O
...	O
https://t.co/AUsIvV7ScV	LINK
Coming	O
in	O
hot	O
bald	BISP
eagle	BISP
in	O
northern	LOC
Utah	LOC
coming	O
into	O
feast	O
upon	O
some	O
fish	O
#Eagle	BISP
#Eagles	BISP
#Baldeagle	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/7h6vNtTyVS	LINK
A	O
Black-capped	BISP
Gnatcatcher	BISP
continues	O
in	O
Santa	LOC
Cruz	LOC
County	LOC
,	O
AZ	LOC
https://t.co/rjq0CJfsDB	LINK
#ABARare	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/YXtRxeSO5o	LINK
Urbanized	O
Black-crowned	BISP
Night	BISP
Heron	BISP
loitering	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
a	O
KFC	ORG
@Oakland	LOC
,	O
California	LOC
#birds	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/gdWojaZyVL	LINK
Chilly	O
Song	O
#Sparrow	BISP
!	O
Happy	O
2018	O
!	O
#birds	O
#birding	O
#texas	LOC
#happynewyear	O
https://t.co/TI4FOQweIp	LINK
Love	O
the	O
contrast	O
of	O
the	O
red	BISP
cardinal	BISP
against	O
the	O
white	O
snow	O
.	O
#ilovenature	O
#ilovephotography	O
#Cardinals	BISP
#birding	O
https://t.co/HdUgwo0xsW	LINK
Black	BISP
Baza	BISP
#birdphotography	O
#bird_brilliance	O
#bird	O
#birds_of_ig	O
#birds_adored	O
...	O
https://t.co/1aWyHGSh3V	LINK
#goldfinch	BISP
#americanGoldfinch	BISP
#CindyTreger	PERS
#photography	O
#artforsale	O
#winter	O
#bird	O
https://t.co/FUKFzaOe7p	LINK
he	O
's	O
a	O
model	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
tell	O
?	O
https://t.co/Les2lytVNm	LINK
#housefinch	BISP
#redheadedfinch	BISP
#finch	BISP
#bird	O
#animal	O
#wildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/XRxzXSXO5R	LINK
woodson	O
is	O
back	O
!	O
https://t.co/3gQ4eOlLcu	LINK
#woodpecker	BISP
#redbelliedwoodpecker	BISP
#bird	O
#animal	O
#wildlife	O
#nature	O
...	O
https://t.co/Oovze0rewN	LINK
May	O
your	O
2018	DATE
be	O
as	O
rewarding	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
times	O
you	O
had	O
in	O
2017	DATE
!	O
Stay	O
warm	O
out	O
there	O
,	O
everyone	O
!	O
#hawk	BISP
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/ZkSZUbqtY4	LINK
On	O
the	O
first	TIME
day	TIME
of	O
2018	DATE
,	O
the	O
Little	BISP
Raven	BISP
-LRB-	O
Corvus	BISP
mellori	BISP
-RRB-	O
family	O
visited	O
the	O
feeders	O
in	O
my	O
front	O
garden	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
,	O
...	O
https://t.co/HlUZgYPy6U	LINK
Blue	BISP
Tit	BISP
Bird	O
Painting	O
Blue	O
Yellow	O
White	O
https://t.co/ksCWHCqckm	LINK
#birds	O
#wildlife	O
#painting	O
https://t.co/kineayqGUQ	LINK
Scientists	O
search	O
for	O
#survivors	O
after	O
the	O
#ThomasFire	O
scorches	O
a	O
#condor	BISP
sanctuary	O
.	O
#Birds	O
#wildfire	O
https://t.co/tXbUOlHjQC	LINK
peregrine	BISP
falcon	BISP
birds	O
#	O
4,000	O
https://t.co/uyfx9ApvZy	LINK
#birds	O
#pets	O
#cheap	O
#forsale	O
#falcon	BISP
#buy	O
#hot	O
#cheapest	O
...	O
https://t.co/CZh4dbuG83	LINK
#bird	O
#egret	BISP
#white	O
#greatwhite	O
#florida	LOC
#great	O
#fineart	O
#dhackett	O
#portrait	O
#american	O
#bluesky	O
#sarasota	O
...	O
https://t.co/72MKsUhFX4	LINK
#bird	O
#egret	BISP
#white	O
#greatwhite	O
#florida	LOC
#great	O
#fineart	O
#dhackett	O
#waterbird	O
https://t.co/ViRVqx8TMq	LINK
Thanks	O
to	O
a	O
Tawny	BISP
Owl	BISP
and	O
an	O
insomniac	O
Pheasant	BISP
,	O
we	O
're	O
winning	O
.	O
Can	O
I	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
bed	O
now	O
?	O
?	O
@BirdTrack	O
#birding	O
#	O
20	O
...	O
https://t.co/pKzpdMzeQr	LINK
Episode	O
#	O
9	O
is	O
out	O
!	O
Suzy	O
is	O
joined	O
by	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
to	O
talk	O
about	O
the	O
penguins	BISP
they	O
saw	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Antar	O
...	O
https://t.co/iUpjY3ByU1	LINK
@OutzideGirl	O
Bald	BISP
Eagle	BISP
and	O
Great	BISP
Egret	BISP
--	O
two	O
of	O
our	O
largest	O
and	O
most	O
magnificent	O
birds	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
side-by-side	O
compariso	O
...	O
https://t.co/6QUYVDbf3q	LINK
Whopper	BISP
swan	BISP
at	O
Welney	LOC
yesterday	TIME
afternoon	TIME
#wildlife	O
#wetlands	O
#birding	O
#norfolk	O
https://t.co/7vcpQknOso	LINK
Excitement	O
today	O
as	O
this	O
absolutely	O
beautiful	O
Grey	BISP
Goshawk	BISP
-LRB-	O
white	BISP
morph	BISP
-RRB-	O
did	O
some	O
hunting	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
.	O
Parrots	BISP
all	O
...	O
https://t.co/jTcT9uWF17	LINK
Felt	BISP
Red	BISP
Cardinals	BISP
,	O
handmade	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
:	O
https://t.co/t4BFhuv8gi	LINK
via	O
@Etsy	O
#Cardinals	BISP
#ShoppersHour	O
#Handmade	O
...	O
https://t.co/8lHmw2B8AI	LINK
Long	BISP
Tailed	BISP
Tit	BISP
#longtailedtit	O
#birdsofinstagram	O
#bird	O
#birds	O
#birdstagram	O
#naturephotography	O
...	O
https://t.co/s0j5ljYLxq	LINK
#birds	O
#gull	BISP
#seagulls	BISP
#beach	O
#ocean	O
#florida	LOC
#fineart	O
#dhackett	O
#reflection	O
#surf	O
#waves	O
https://t.co/AE7EnZZVOO	LINK
https://t.co/GJo8DU4o0Q	LINK
Peacock	BISP
Feathers	O
Painting	O
String	O
Art	O
Original	O
Large	O
Abstract	O
https://t.co/sU9rZFDrTL	LINK
#birds	O
#art	O
#painting	O
...	O
https://t.co/yeD5JlHSgo	LINK
A	O
Little	O
Chickadee	BISP
-	O
https://t.co/1RxgbIJY5M	LINK
#wildlifephotography	O
#nature	O
#bird	O
by	O
#pure_p4	O
via	O
@c0nvey	O
https://t.co/8B6Hw17DXM	LINK
FOUND	O
Bird	O
Budgie	BISP
in	O
Bedworth	LOC
Warwickshire	LOC
https://t.co/eeDT04Va82	LINK
#bedworth	O
#	O
#bird	O
#petregister	O
pls	O
RT	O
MISSING	O
Bird	O
Parrot	BISP
,	O
Parakeet	BISP
from	O
Okehampton	LOC
Devon	LOC
https://t.co/N7JO6NYDgp	LINK
#okehampton	O
#	O
#bird	O
#petregister	O
pls	O
RT	O
Spotted	O
male	SEX
Bullfinch	BISP
in	O
the	O
garden	O
earlier	TIME
!	O
First	O
bird	O
sighting	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
!	O
#Bullfinch	BISP
#NewYear	O
#Bird	O
#RSPB	O
https://t.co/72PvKP7wts	LINK
A	O
Pretty	O
Blue	BISP
#Bird	BISP
-	O
#iPad	O
Protective	O
Case	O
and	O
#Skins	O
-	O
https://t.co/6JwLVPX8DI	LINK
https://t.co/V3n8cwoqDY	LINK
Mmm	O
.	O
A	O
spot	O
of	O
fish	O
for	O
#supper	O
?	O
#fishing	O
#pondheron	BISP
#bird	O
#colombo	LOC
#wetland	LOC
#park	LOC
#srilanka	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/a2c9HgADxu	LINK
-	O
swan	LOC
https://t.co/vXRCQvm2Ez	LINK
#bird	O
Cardinal	BISP
.	O
...	O
#bird	O
#birds	O
#nature	O
#birdphotography	O
#wildlife	O
#wildlifephotography	O
#birdsofinstagram	O
#animal	O
...	O
https://t.co/hxmlm8Pzbh	LINK
Sandpiper	BISP
in	O
flight	O
.	O
#flyingbird	O
#bird	O
#birds	O
#nature	O
#flying	O
#photography	O
#birdphotography	O
...	O
https://t.co/Pc0utJXXkp	LINK
#birder	O
problems	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
red-bellied	BISP
woodpecker	BISP
&	O
a	O
yellow-bellied	BISP
sapsucker	BISP
on	O
#feeder	O
at	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
y	O
...	O
https://t.co/V4skbwW3WP	LINK
@WRY999	O
@NewsOn6	O
@KTULNews	O
@KJRH2HD	O
@MikeCollierWX	O
My	O
first	O
bird	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
2018	DATE
-	O
Goldfinch	BISP
!	O
What	O
's	O
yours	O
?	O
#Birding	O
#FirstBird18	O
Barn	BISP
owl	BISP
flying	O
in	O
the	O
snow	O
in	O
watercolour	O
size	O
3.5	O
&#034;	O
x	O
2.5	O
&#034;	O
original	O
art	O
ACEO	O
https://t.co/4lcpDH4WGs	LINK
vi	O
...	O
https://t.co/YYcu23RetB	LINK
https://t.co/Vxj6EvASOL	LINK
#robin	O
#homedecor	O
#Christmas	O
#watercolour	O
#bird	O
#art	O
#gift	O
#ornithology	O
#garden	O
#gardentoday	O
Eider	BISP
Ducks	BISP
in	O
flight	O
#eider	BISP
#eiderduck	BISP
#flight	O
#bird	O
#rattray	O
#aberdeenshire	O
#scotland	LOC
https://t.co/RRd1OroMrK	LINK
https://t.co/kbI3lxHvNx	LINK
great	O
pictures	O
of	O
Clarice	O
today	O
at	O
the	O
feeder	O
.	O
#redbelliedwoodpecker	BISP
#birding	O
#nature	O
#birds	O
#wildlife	O
https://t.co/YDMHTDKc2W	LINK
My	O
A	O
to	O
Z	O
park	O
activities	O
for	O
today	O
are	O
#Birding	O
and	O
#Boating	O
This	O
summer	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
see	O
thousands	O
of	O
#purplemartins	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/x8qUTbXozF	LINK
Happy	O
New	O
Year	O
!	O
Some	O
morning	O
bird	O
floofs	O
here	O
.	O
White-throated	BISP
sparrow	BISP
,	O
tufted	BISP
titmouse	BISP
,	O
female	SEX
cardinal	BISP
,	O
mourning	O
d	O
...	O
https://t.co/zNa0uHg6zc	LINK
Last	O
#birding	O
spot	O
of	O
2017	DATE
:	O
Chewacla	LOC
State	LOC
Park	LOC
in	O
#Alabama	LOC
.	O
#waterfall	O
#nature	O
https://t.co/t3Nq8Psbob	LINK
During	TIME
January	TIME
I	O
'm	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
turning	O
the	O
pages	O
of	O
this	O
1950s	DATE
Ladybird	O
Book	O
of	O
British	O
Birds	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
's	O
changed	O
...	O
https://t.co/Hnf2liALX5	LINK
Cranes	BISP
at	O
sunrise	O
@stefanholmPHOTO	O
#photo	O
#	O
500px	O
#crane	O
#bird	O
https://t.co/ZRKfk4sdfq	LINK
https://t.co/gcSR1toPOo	LINK
Roseate	BISP
Spoonbills	BISP
on	O
the	O
marshes	O
near	O
Rockport	LOC
.	O
Follow	O
along	O
on	O
Whooping	BISP
Crane	BISP
Morning	TIME
:	O
https://t.co/wt0QIS7ROK…	LINK
https://t.co/F6CH9FKqQZ	LINK
The	O
other	O
day	O
I	O
spent	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
chasing	O
sparrows	BISP
around	O
a	O
flooded	O
field	O
and	O
was	O
wholly	O
unsuccessful	O
in	O
getting	O
ph	O
...	O
https://t.co/QlnKWNTjlg	LINK
Ladder-backed	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
on	O
my	O
patio	O
today	O
.	O
#birds	O
#birding	O
#Texas	LOC
#nature	O
https://t.co/rSAIexZmXO	LINK
Markeaton	LOC
Brook	LOC
-LRB-	O
SK3238	O
-RRB-	O
2	NUMB
Little	BISP
Egret	BISP
#derbyshire	O
#birding	O
Ambergate	LOC
-LRB-	O
SK3451	O
-RRB-	O
40	NUMB
Mandarin	BISP
#derbyshire	O
#birding	O
Hummingbird	BISP
at	O
my	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
photographing	O
#hummingbirds	BISP
in	O
#WestHollywood	LOC
#California	LOC
for	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
...	O
https://t.co/FTbE6ThGe0	LINK
Yellow-rumped	BISP
#Warbler	BISP
eating	O
poison	O
oak	O
seeds	O
.	O
#birds	O
#songbirds	O
#birding	O
#birdphotography	O
#naturephotography	O
https://t.co/WRqcvSNekd	LINK
Northern	BISP
Fulmars	BISP
at	O
Newhaven	LOC
#bird	O
#northernfulmar	BISP
#fulmar	BISP
#sussex	O
#newhaven	O
#birding	O
#birdwatching	O
#tubenose	BISP
https://t.co/PuooH43e59	LINK
A	O
is	O
for	O
the	O
Abyssinian	BISP
roller	BISP
-LRB-	O
Coracias	BISP
abyssinicus	BISP
-RRB-	O
!	O
This	O
colorful	O
pal	O
is	O
named	O
after	O
the	O
aerial	O
acrobatics	O
it	O
an	O
...	O
https://t.co/rnM6TTkxtK	LINK
The	O
first	O
DOPE	O
NOPE	O
of	O
2018	DATE
is	O
here	O
!	O
Check	O
out	O
the	O
Shoebill	BISP
at	O
https://t.co/iRfJWu0Wbi	LINK
!	O
#shoebill	BISP
#bird	O
#dopenope	O
...	O
https://t.co/ocD2yP3YjT	LINK
First	O
bird	O
of	O
2018	DATE
,	O
a	O
fluffed	O
up	O
American	BISP
Robin	BISP
poking	O
around	O
near	O
a	O
frozen	O
pond	O
in	O
a	O
neighbor	O
's	O
yard	O
on	O
a	O
cold	O
wi	O
...	O
https://t.co/BevJgFkUCW	LINK
Ooh	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
picture	O
in	O
time	O
but	O
I	O
just	O
saw	O
what	O
I	O
'm	O
pretty	O
certain	O
was	O
a	O
#gyrfalcon	BISP
across	O
...	O
https://t.co/T2v482CDqE	LINK
Loved	O
seeing	O
kingfisher	BISP
today	TIME
,	O
unless	O
you	O
smarties	O
say	O
NO	O
@Team_eBird	O
@audubon	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/XNNGgRsPii	LINK
Application	O
deadline	O
is	O
Jan	O
14	O
.	O
These	O
#PipingPlovers	BISP
need	O
our	O
help	O
to	O
continue	O
their	O
comeback	O
in	O
Ontario	LOC
!	O
#birding	O
...	O
https://t.co/S0Zd4IeCzH	LINK
It	O
crows	O
at	TIME
dawn	TIME
.	O
#victoria	O
#britishcolumbia	LOC
#pacificocean	LOC
#bird	O
#crow	BISP
If	O
Victoria	O
ever	O
wants	O
...	O
https://t.co/3m4tB8W0QU	LINK
``	O
Bubo	BISP
scandiacus	BISP
''	O
,	O
#Cadiz	LOC
,	O
#Spain	LOC
,	O
2015	DATE
.	O
#owls	BISP
#birds	O
#Spanish	O
https://t.co/VRJ6HVTUtT	LINK
A	O
visitation	O
of	O
black	BISP
skimmers	BISP
.	O
#birding	O
#winter	O
#wings	O
https://t.co/hSMi6GS4XO	LINK
Excited	O
to	O
start	O
the	O
new	O
year	O
in	O
beautiful	O
Santa	LOC
Barbara	LOC
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
first	O
Black	BISP
Skimmers	BISP
!	O
Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
m	O
...	O
https://t.co/k6pJHkx5wz	LINK
My	O
first	O
bird	O
of	O
2018	DATE
was	O
a	O
House	BISP
Finch	BISP
?	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
last	O
bird	O
of	O
2017	DATE
was	O
Horned	BISP
Lark	BISP
?	O
.	O
Good	O
#birding	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
2018	DATE
...	O
https://t.co/e6TdV2g33v	LINK
Blue	BISP
#Bird	BISP
-	O
#ShowerCurtain	O
71	O
''	O
by	O
74	O
''	O
-	O
https://t.co/zUOG9j2MDz	LINK
https://t.co/Zt6FqFvun3	LINK
A	O
seagull	BISP
trying	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
's	O
friend	O
is	O
simply	O
amazing	O
.	O
???	O
#seagull	BISP
#eagle	BISP
#wildlifeonearth	O
#wildlife_seekers	O
...	O
https://t.co/Iw6XcXZY8e	LINK
#Haifax	LOC
#Dartmouth	LOC
#NovaScotia	LOC
#Canad	O
#BlueJay	BISP
#Birds	O
Shot	O
On	O
The	O
#IPhoneX	O
https://t.co/XvYKF5wuxg	LINK
Gaviota	BISP
Cahuil	BISP
,	O
gaviota	O
Chilota	O
#bird	O
#gaviota	O
#instagram	O
#instalike	O
#instagood	O
#nikon5200	O
#fly	O
...	O
https://t.co/Yyd9MEOzft	LINK
Someone	O
saw	O
a	O
golden	BISP
eagle	BISP
in	O
Snohomish	LOC
today	TIME
,	O
so	O
now	O
I	O
am	O
reevaluating	O
every	O
damn	O
immature	O
eagle	BISP
I	O
saw	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
...	O
https://t.co/8ZywwSa4qi	LINK
Great	BISP
Spotted	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
at	O
Warnham	LOC
#nature	O
Reserve	O
@HorshamWildlife	O
c	O
@NarrowboatDave	O
#photography	O
#birds	O
#travel	O
https://t.co/lG7hbJKQ2X	LINK
New	O
Fischers	BISP
Lovebirds	BISP
settled	O
in	O
quick	O
#aviculture	O
#aviary	O
#lovebirds	BISP
#fischerslovebird	BISP
#birds	O
https://t.co/BbBJFSxILQ	LINK
A	O
Hawfinch	BISP
has	O
just	O
been	O
confirmed	O
in	O
Anchorage	LOC
County	LOC
,	O
Alaska	LOC
!	O
-LRB-	O
CODE	O
4	O
-RRB-	O
https://t.co/FbJZ07z4OL	LINK
#ABARare	O
#birding	O
Kestrel	BISP
by	O
Mubi.A	O
-	O
https://t.co/vu9Dd9eaNy	LINK
#YouPic	O
#photography	O
#bird	O
#animal	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
Fall	O
Play	O
...	O
`	O
The	O
Morning	O
#Stretch	O
#Racine	O
Country	O
#Canon	O
#TeamCanon	O
#Birds	O
#Birding	O
#Sandhill	BISP
#Crane	BISP
New	O
study	O
on	O
evaluating	O
Umbrella	BISP
species	O
using	O
niche	O
overlap	O
.	O
Umbrella	BISP
species	O
is	O
a	O
selected	O
species	O
indicating	O
an	O
...	O
https://t.co/nwTP7ZlZ7C	LINK
Immune	O
condition	O
and	O
blood	O
parasites	O
in	O
three	O
sparrow	BISP
species	O
with	O
different	O
migratory	O
status	O
in	O
central	LOC
Mexico	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/233ruEbaNE	LINK
An	O
inexpensive	O
satellite-download	O
GPS	O
receiver	O
for	O
wildlife	O
:	O
field	O
trial	O
on	O
black	BISP
swans	BISP
https://t.co/r1tLtHmqb2…	LINK
https://t.co/9vQ92IvT9r	LINK
Apparent	O
survival	O
and	O
long-term	O
population	O
growth	O
rate	O
of	O
the	O
Kentish	BISP
Plover	BISP
in	O
Mallorca	LOC
,	O
Balearic	LOC
Archipelago	LOC
,	O
Spa	O
...	O
https://t.co/oTze8Kj0qj	LINK
Change	O
of	O
feeding	O
strategy	O
prior	O
to	O
migration	O
:	O
a	O
comparative	O
diet	O
analysis	O
in	O
the	O
Lesser	BISP
Kestrel	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/c9F2PBZ2t1	LINK
Distribution	O
and	O
breeding	O
ecology	O
of	O
the	O
Ferruginous	BISP
Duck	O
-LRB-	O
Aythya	BISP
nyroca	BISP
-RRB-	O
in	O
Algeria	LOC
https://t.co/7fFSHUcAIW	LINK
@ostrichJAO	O
#ornithology	O
•	O
Canards	BISP
colvert	BISP
/	O
Anas	BISP
platyrhynchos	BISP
•	O
#oiseau	O
#canard	BISP
#duck	BISP
#migrateur	O
#bird	O
#songbird	O
#bunting	O
#animal	O
...	O
https://t.co/3TQciXRnix	LINK
#Dunnock	BISP
#Bude	LOC
#Cornwall	LOC
#wildlife	O
#Birdwatching	O
#nature	O
#birds	O
@Natures_Voice	O
@wildlife_uk	O
@Birds_UK	O
@wildlifenet	O
...	O
https://t.co/XmZ6hjtSAy	LINK
Young	O
enthusiast	O
#Hes	O
back	O
Love	O
?	O
Rambo	O
lorikeet	BISP
#lorikeet	BISP
#birds	O
#loveforbirds	O
#birdsaspet	O
#handfeeding	O
...	O
https://t.co/3QlLlLdcX9	LINK
Gulls	BISP
hovering	O
over	O
a	O
frozen	O
lake	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
#winter	O
#birds	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
#frost	O
landscape	O
#photography	O
...	O
https://t.co/ENMcZVCXQV	LINK
Blue	BISP
Billed	BISP
Duck	BISP
.	O
#art	O
#artist	O
#australia	O
#illustration	O
#birds	O
#design	O
#handmade	O
...	O
https://t.co/LdtNgEGOr0	LINK
Female	SEX
Splendid	BISP
Fairy-wren	BISP
-LRB-	O
Malurus	BISP
splendens	BISP
-RRB-	O
Walpole	LOC
,	O
WA	LOC
#WildOz	O
#birding	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/hOVf15YFrY	LINK
A	NUMB
pair	NUMB
of	NUMB
#ducks	BISP
asleep	O
at	O
@chatsworthhouse	O
#peakdistrict	O
buy	O
as	O
a	O
print	O
here	O
https://t.co/mF9ob7AQqR	LINK
#birding	O
#ad	O
...	O
https://t.co/gR6JWC64oo	LINK
In	O
Borneo	LOC
,	O
Greater	BISP
Coucals	BISP
are	O
captured	O
and	O
used	O
in	O
traditional	O
medicine	O
-LRB-	O
Yogesh	PERS
Kumar	PERS
-RRB-	O
https://t.co/lcEZhpSMHS…	LINK
https://t.co/UJwYHVLr2n	LINK
Evening	O
Grace	O
Mute	BISP
Swan	BISP
at	O
sunset	O
.	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
#morning	TIME
#newyear	O
#birding	O
@Natures_Voice	O
@_BTO	O
...	O
https://t.co/HuSRgkFm5K	LINK
Another	O
#lifer	O
from	O
yesterday	O
's	O
outing	O
to	O
@Algonquin_PP	O
.	O
Red	BISP
crossbill	BISP
.	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/EuNeLce7SJ	LINK
Bath	O
towel	O
with	O
Owl	BISP
in	O
glasses	O
machine	O
embroidery	O
https://t.co/HxjbCzYgJc	LINK
:	O
Atelierul	O
cu	O
Broderii	O
#bathtowel	O
#owl	O
...	O
https://t.co/9TbuWssKx2	LINK
A	O
great	O
blog	O
post	O
by	O
@dferbel	O
on	O
his	O
@ESAEcology	O
paper	O
https://t.co/Wl6THbR7WO	LINK
for	O
#theBOUblog	O
#vultures	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/Oenjut73f1	LINK
New	O
on	O
#theBOUblog	O
:	O
Too	O
close	O
for	O
comfort	O
?	O
Coloniality	O
and	O
density	O
dependence	O
in	O
vultures	BISP
,	O
by	O
@dferbel	O
...	O
https://t.co/TOZKPnumEw	LINK
From	O
@IBIS_journal	O
2016	O
|	O
High	O
brood	O
patch	O
temperature	O
of	O
less	O
colourful	O
,	O
less	O
pheomelanic	O
female	SEX
Barn	BISP
Swallows	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/gx2jd4WxFb	LINK
The	O
invisible	O
bird	O
:	O
what	O
makes	O
the	O
#nightjar	BISP
a	O
camouflage	O
https://t.co/X7oEPBhXxj	LINK
#ornithology	O
@CosmosMagazine	O
https://t.co/V4rA2JbpUA	LINK
This	O
red-tailed	BISP
hawk	BISP
was	O
so	O
well	O
camouflaged	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
within	O
6	O
feet	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
seeing	O
it	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
enjoying	O
a	O
...	O
https://t.co/4ZucXBvl2i	LINK
I	O
'm	O
feeling	O
this	O
look	O
?	O
#housesparrow	O
#female	SEX
#bird	O
#sparrow	BISP
#songbird	O
#instabird	O
...	O
https://t.co/Rk6bbw2Whs	LINK
#Garden	O
#photography	O
and	O
#birding	O
Orange-winged	BISP
Pytilia	BISP
-LRB-	O
Golden-backed	BISP
Pytilia	BISP
-RRB-	O
He	O
&	O
She	O
#Kigali	LOC
#Rwanda	LOC
https://t.co/B2vjhS9v0r	LINK
OTG	O
crop	O
and	O
edit	O
photo	O
on	O
android	O
phone.no	O
longer	O
bringing	O
laptop	O
for	O
guiding	O
trips	O
.	O
Asian	BISP
Pied	BISP
Starling	BISP
on	O
the	O
lo	O
...	O
https://t.co/d4csYPkLUr	LINK
Not	O
sure	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
real	O
or	O
a	O
dream	O
.	O
4am	O
,	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
and	O
#Eastern	BISP
#Screech	BISP
#owl	BISP
in	O
yard	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
photo	O
at	O
...	O
https://t.co/IGlddhFBCE	LINK
A	O
male	SEX
Olive-backed	BISP
Sunbird	BISP
perching	O
on	O
Ixora	O
thua	O
afternoon	TIME
.	O
#sunbird	O
#birding	O
#birdwatching	O
#nature2pixel	O
...	O
https://t.co/YYxcxW92wT	LINK
#theBOUblog	O
revisited	O
|	O
The	O
point	O
of	O
a	O
Guillemot	BISP
's	O
egg	O
https://t.co/4wXFavZDBc	LINK
From	O
this	O
@IBIS_journal	O
paper	O
...	O
https://t.co/v9SfmNDjvi	LINK
Ridiculously	O
cold	O
this	O
AM	TIME
around	O
Chicago	LOC
.	O
9	O
below	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
Common	BISP
Redpoll	BISP
in	O
our	O
yard	O
for	O
the	O
1st	O
time	O
...	O
https://t.co/h5DwgwbDpt	LINK
Hummingbird	BISP
floating	O
by	O
my	O
window	O
#WestHollywood	LOC
#California	LOC
.	O
#hollyweed	O
#hollywood	LOC
#design	O
#graphicdesign	O
...	O
https://t.co/DGASV0FCJt	LINK
#bird	O
#coopershawk	BISP
#raptor	O
#hawk	BISP
#predator	O
#florida	LOC
#fineart	O
#dhackett	O
#audubon	O
https://t.co/Vqk6cN2jDr	LINK
https://t.co/BPGEuxotlt	LINK
Black-winged	BISP
Stilt	BISP
,	O
The	LOC
Gambia	LOC
.	O
#thegambia	LOC
#gambiaexperience	O
#birds	O
#bird	O
#wildlifephotography	O
...	O
https://t.co/4Llu8ZR4Zg	LINK
Female	SEX
purple	BISP
finch	BISP
#nature	O
#photography	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/J9sXcyZx0W	LINK
A	O
blue-necked	BISP
tanager	BISP
?	O
-LRB-	O
Tangara	BISP
cyanicollis	BISP
-RRB-	O
,	O
photographed	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
students	O
in	O
Mindo	LOC
,	O
Ecuador	LOC
at	O
a	O
chocolate	O
...	O
https://t.co/fGFXuowFJa	LINK
Got	O
ta	O
take	O
it	O
slow	O
today	O
...	O
need	O
help	O
to	O
pick	O
your	O
next	O
holiday	O
?	O
Check	O
out	O
https://t.co/O1hyfmfWdK	LINK
#travelblogger	O
...	O
https://t.co/MElzH62Fh8	LINK
Bewick	BISP
's	BISP
Wren	BISP
-LRB-	O
Thryomanes	BISP
bewickii	BISP
-RRB-	O
-	O
?	O
#BewicksWren	BISP
#Wren	BISP
#BEWR	O
#ThryomanesBewickii	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/Usbd3zjlNA	LINK
interesting	O
story	O
of	O
tracking	O
down	O
a	NUMB
pair	NUMB
of	NUMB
california	BISP
condors	BISP
&	O
their	O
wild-born	O
chick	O
despite	O
the	O
thomas	O
wildfire	O
...	O
https://t.co/n61w3gXSth	LINK
Pigeon	BISP
ramier	BISP
-LRB-	O
Columba	BISP
palumbus	BISP
-	O
Common	BISP
Wood	BISP
Pigeon	BISP
-RRB-	O
sous	O
la	O
pluie	O
#oiseau	O
#birds	O
#birding	O
#birdphotography	O
-LRB-	O
...	O
https://t.co/VXTayvmNAh	LINK
That	O
mockingbird	BISP
I	O
saw	O
on	O
zoo	O
grounds	O
mid-December	TIME
is	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Steve	PERS
,	O
still	O
flitting	O
around	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
.	O
...	O
https://t.co/nwu1zK2yaa	LINK
My	O
first	O
drawing	O
of	O
2018	DATE
has	O
begun	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
busy	O
sketching	O
out	O
this	O
green	BISP
woodpecker	BISP
tonight	TIME
.	O
#bird	O
#sketch	O
https://t.co/dC2E9tDWFM	LINK
It	O
's	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
.	O
I	O
'd	O
be	O
a	O
#Macaw	O
-	O
a	O
#colourful	O
#NewWorldOrder	O
#parrot	BISP
.	O
What	O
#species	O
of	O
#bird	O
would	O
you	O
...	O
https://t.co/3YaLp8prMH	LINK
new	O
species	O
online	O
:	O
Eurasian	BISP
Siskin	BISP
https://t.co/CbWkE8vemJ	LINK
#birdmigration	O
#birdID	O
#birdIDguide	O
#songbird	O
...	O
https://t.co/pLLkJ5aKX5	LINK
new	O
species	O
online	O
:	O
Sanderling	BISP
Calidris	BISP
alba	BISP
https://t.co/SqMJnceOdt	LINK
#birdmigration	O
#birdID	O
#birdIDguide	O
...	O
https://t.co/N1mmKOCGzg	LINK
Intratropical	O
movements	O
as	O
a	O
beneficial	O
strategy	O
for	O
Palearctic	O
#migratorybirds	O
@RSocPublishing	O
@rytikerttunen	O
...	O
https://t.co/R8X4EoLrZ4	LINK
RT	RTWT
@AukJournal	AUTH
:	O
From	O
2016	O
:	O
Age	O
structure	O
of	O
Black-backed	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
populations	O
in	O
burned	O
forests	O
https://t.co/MuVK4Jzgej	LINK
#OA	O
#ornithology	O
...	O
1967	DATE
Vintage	O
Bird	O
Egg	O
Print	O
.	O
Oystercatcher	BISP
Godwit	BISP
Avocet	BISP
Eggs	O
Illustration	O
.	O
Gift	O
for	O
Birders	O
.	O
Oology	O
.	O
#Ornithology	O
...	O
https://t.co/KDDMlXcZjr	LINK
RT	RTWT
@chris4nature	AUTH
:	O
Successive	O
Peregrine	BISP
falcons	BISP
in	O
northern	LOC
Greenland	LOC
have	O
continuously	O
used	O
a	O
nest	O
site	O
for	O
for	O
2,500	O
years	O
#ornithology	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@WilsonOrnithSoc	AUTH
:	O
Flushing	O
responses	O
of	O
Golden	BISP
Eagles	BISP
-LRB-	O
Aquila	BISP
chrysaetos	BISP
-RRB-	O
in	O
response	O
to	O
recreation	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/KnuUHpZOCY	LINK
Black-winged	BISP
Stilt	BISP
,	O
The	LOC
Gambia	LOC
.	O
#birds	O
#birdphotography	O
#wildlife	O
#wildlifephotography	O
...	O
https://t.co/lVl0KFHb1r	LINK
RT	RTWT
@HistSciArt	AUTH
:	O
From	O
#Flamingos	BISP
and	O
#RoseateSpoonbills	BISP
to	O
#RosyStarlings	BISP
and	O
#MajorMitchellsCockatoos	BISP
--	O
#PinkBirds	O
are	O
my	O
favorite	O
#birds	O
!	O
...	O
From	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
Bullfinch	BISP
in	O
a	O
Rowan	O
Tree	O
.	O
Warm	O
colours	O
for	O
a	O
cold	O
day	O
#birds	O
#goldleaf	O
...	O
https://t.co/jMoXRZYFTl	LINK
The	O
Indian	BISP
Roller	BISP
-LRB-	O
Coracias	BISP
benghalensis	BISP
-RRB-	O
-	O
formerly	O
also	O
called	O
the	O
Blue	BISP
Jay	BISP
-	O
is	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
roller	O
family	O
.	O
I	O
...	O
https://t.co/JsgBKFAXbU	LINK
My	O
bird	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Male	SEX
Bullfinches	BISP
are	O
a	O
common	O
visitor	O
to	O
@CeeegeBirds	O
's	O
garden	O
.	O
https://t.co/aGgw1psnQ1	LINK
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/SPqflE1rKd	LINK
RT	RTWT
@QuakerNana	AUTH
:	O
#birds	O
They	O
are	O
amazing	O
.	O
Nothing	O
like	O
a	O
shock	O
of	O
a	O
cardinal	BISP
's	O
red	O
against	O
the	O
snow	O
.	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
https://t.co/zk4WnAcw…	LINK
Honiton	LOC
Weather	O
Now	TIME
...	O
#WeatherReport	O
#Honiton	LOC
#gardenbirds	O
#birding	O
#birdphotography	O
#Goldfinch	BISP
#Greenfinch	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/QplEt6NlVD	LINK
RT	RTWT
@greenfieldsimag	AUTH
:	O
Pied	BISP
Wagtail	BISP
.	O
#Piedwagtail	BISP
#ukbirds	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/5E1UqP54ZC	LINK
RT	RTWT
@SerenaVachon	AUTH
:	O
Bluebird	BISP
#wildlife	O
#photography	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/UqY9tKZMhx	LINK
On	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
this	O
beauty	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
missed	O
-	O
#GiantEagleOwl	BISP
-	O
most	O
#Stylish	O
#bird	O
with	O
the	O
#pink	O
#eyeshadow	O
?	O
...	O
https://t.co/ZzS6GPyK8T	LINK
A	O
gorgeous	O
male	SEX
Regal	BISP
Sunbird	BISP
.	O
An	O
Albertine	LOC
Rift	LOC
Valley	LOC
Endemic	O
seen	O
in	O
SW	LOC
Uganda	LOC
last	TIME
year	TIME
.	O
@BirdingEcotours	O
...	O
https://t.co/BrFUqUqF53	LINK
Pinned	O
to	O
Instagram	O
Pictures	O
on	O
@Pinterest	O
:	O
Mindfullnes	O
...	O
#nature	O
#vulture	BISP
#wildlifephotography	O
#wildlife	O
#birding	O
...	O
https://t.co/s5n9SGllSN	LINK
Mindfullnes	O
...	O
#nature	O
#vulture	BISP
#wildlifephotography	O
#wildlife	O
#birding	O
#birds	O
#raptors	O
#davidmsfoto	O
#wildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/H6xylsPHlA	LINK
@ChrisGPackham	O
Black-winged	BISP
Stilt	BISP
,	O
Gloucestershire	LOC
...	O
.	O
OK	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Slimbridge	LOC
in	O
the	O
tropical	O
house	O
but	O
that	O
's	O
...	O
https://t.co/fBpkODo8GX	LINK
RT	RTWT
@AllThatWildlife	AUTH
:	O
The	O
Clay-colored	BISP
Thrush	BISP
is	O
Costa	LOC
Rica	LOC
's	O
national	O
#bird	O
.	O
https://t.co/Maps80aEM8	LINK
#birding	O
#	O
2017PIFSMBC	O
#CostaRica	LOC
htt	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@AllThatWildlife	AUTH
:	O
Though	O
plain-looking	O
,	O
the	O
Clay-colored	BISP
Thrush	BISP
was	O
chosen	O
as	O
national	O
#bird	O
of	O
#CostaRica	LOC
in	O
large	O
part	O
because	O
of	O
its	O
...	O
Robin	BISP
#photography	O
#NaturePhotography	O
#birds	O
#winter	O
https://t.co/Yj0CW0xYKe	LINK
Robin	BISP
redbreast	O
#birdsofinsta	O
#birdphotography	O
#bird	O
#birds	O
#robin	BISP
#robins	BISP
#avian	O
#feathers	O
...	O
https://t.co/cVqfyk9vTL	LINK
Pigeon	BISP
-	O
2	NUMB
#pigeon	BISP
#park	O
#hiroo	O
#arisugawapark	LOC
#bird	O
#peace	O
#	O
?	O
#	O
??	O
#moment	O
#	O
??	O
#	O
??????????	O
#	O
??	O
...	O
https://t.co/n0rYAi4LEJ	LINK
For	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
I	O
am	O
offering	O
my	O
original	O
hand	O
woodburned	O
Great	BISP
Horned	BISP
Owl	BISP
for	O
a	O
discount	O
.	O
Message	O
to	O
own	O
.	O
...	O
https://t.co/jLXv5zrllg	LINK
#robin	BISP
#penandink	O
#drawing	O
#researching	O
for	O
my	O
next	O
group	O
of	O
#paintings	O
#birds	O
#winter	O
#art	O
#nature	O
https://t.co/KLO0UIpMKE	LINK
Dark	O
eyed	O
junco	BISP
#Backyardbirds	O
#birdphotography	O
#Nature	O
#Photography	O
#winter	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/CPIL2yaGBW	LINK
The	O
#bullfinches	BISP
are	O
back	O
!	O
After	O
a	O
two	O
year	O
absents	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Did	O
n't	O
manage	O
to	O
get	O
any	O
GOOD	O
...	O
https://t.co/GW3GciTOe0	LINK
Happy	O
Spring	DATE
2014	DATE
-	O
Sparrows	BISP
Dance	O
of	O
Life	O
https://t.co/Smtdadm7E4	LINK
https://t.co/lFSe0zDF4c	LINK
#Nature	O
#Photography	O
#Birds	O
RT	RTWT
@RichardMcLellan	AUTH
:	O
A	O
beaut-looking	O
Fan-tailed	BISP
Cuckoo	BISP
-LRB-	O
Cacomantis	BISP
flabelliformis	BISP
-RRB-	O
Walpole	LOC
,	O
WA	LOC
#WildOz	O
#birds	O
#birdwatching	O
https://t.co/BW…	LINK
RT	RTWT
@RichardMcLellan	AUTH
:	O
My	O
Bird	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
New	BISP
Holland	BISP
Honeyeater	BISP
-LRB-	O
Phylidonyris	BISP
novaehollandiae	BISP
-RRB-	O
https://t.co/eP0G0M4dRo	LINK
#WildOz	O
#birds	O
#bird	O
...	O
Cormorant	BISP
#LakeMeadows	LOC
#Billericay	LOC
#Essex	LOC
this	TIME
morning	TIME
#birds	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/WZ9QX9NxYT	LINK
RT	RTWT
@gpool67	AUTH
:	O
Beautiful	O
green	BISP
heron	BISP
on	O
our	O
#SanibelIsland	LOC
pond	O
.	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
#birds	O
#nature	O
#Florida	LOC
https://t.co/6nYjdwirdP	LINK
3	NUMB
Bird	O
Nesting	O
Terrace	O
https://t.co/oV4JjNk2Ve	LINK
#birds	O
#birdhouse	O
#garden	O
#birdwatching	O
Peacock	BISP
Feathers	O
Painting	O
String	O
Art	O
Original	O
Large	O
Abstract	O
https://t.co/sU9rZFDrTL	LINK
#birds	O
#art	O
#painting	O
...	O
https://t.co/azOlZYcfOA	LINK
Three	NUMB
Little	O
Ducks	BISP
https://t.co/1Qup5feKj6	LINK
#photofolio	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/oRMT1aMRgw	LINK
Sandhill	BISP
Crane	BISP
-LRB-	O
Antigone	BISP
canadensis	BISP
-RRB-	O
by	O
Scott	PERS
Helfrich	PERS
#photography	O
#bird	O
#wildlife	O
#NorthAmerican	LOC
#sandhillcrane	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/oc2mkLSjyH	LINK
#Owls	BISP
:	O
a	O
most	O
mysterious	O
#bird	O
https://t.co/ITkQVuRuZu	LINK
@AlexisinNH	O
@BlackIrishI	O
@BlissTabitha	O
@jayme0509	O
...	O
https://t.co/KY3xtxXj15	LINK
RT	RTWT
@Nature_Spot	AUTH
:	O
What	O
's	O
Around	O
:	O
Redwing	BISP
,	O
Turdus	BISP
iliacus	BISP
.	O
Photo	O
Jonesboy1	O
Learn	O
more	O
:	O
https://t.co/1VXxoTo6Zs	LINK
#birds	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
htt	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@CreatureCandy9	AUTH
:	O
Short	O
eared	O
owl	BISP
by	O
Frank	PERS
Wildman	PERS
.	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
#photography	O
#birds	O
#owl	BISP
https://t.co/m9A6ETYqzA	LINK
https://t.co/G4EzF…	LINK
Tweety	O
pie	O
the	O
cute	O
yellow	O
canary	BISP
#bird	O
being	O
showered	O
with	O
#love	O
???	O
Hand	O
embroidery	O
&	O
art	O
pencil	O
#mixedmedia	O
...	O
https://t.co/EwzxKPfnU3	LINK
RT	RTWT
@sofrenchvintage	AUTH
:	O
1967	DATE
Vintage	O
Cukoo	BISP
,	O
Warbler	BISP
,	O
Passerine	BISP
,	O
Wrens	BISP
Egg	O
Print	O
.	O
Eggs	O
Identification	O
Chart	O
.	O
Oology	O
.	O
#Ornithology	O
Wall	O
Art	O
.	O
htt	O
...	O
Tiny	O
blue	O
#beauty	O
walking	O
up	O
&	O
down	O
along	O
the	O
#tree	O
trunk	O
!	O
#Velvet	O
fronted	O
#Nuthatch	BISP
#forest	O
#Ganeshgudi	O
#colors	O
of	O
...	O
https://t.co/OGXufNoj4N	LINK
RT	RTWT
@dlsdigitalarts	AUTH
:	O
A	O
baby	O
Channel-billed	BISP
Cuckoo	BISP
hiding	O
up	O
in	O
trees	O
waiting	O
for	O
food	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
#dlsdigitalarts	O
#cuckoo	BISP
#birdsofinstagram	O
#bird	O
#	O
b	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@cariadferch	AUTH
:	O
Great	BISP
Horned	BISP
Owl	BISP
#NationalBirdDay	O
#illustration	O
#animals	O
#birds	O
#tagdesvogels	O
#owls	BISP
https://t.co/MwYmPLijR5	LINK
RT	RTWT
@Mayblossoming	AUTH
:	O
Robbie	O
the	O
robin	BISP
is	O
strutting	O
his	O
stuff	O
today	O
,	O
seeing	O
as	O
it	O
's	O
national	O
bird	O
day	O
?	O
#nationalbirdday	O
#robin	BISP
#bird	O
#childre	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@FayLouise33	AUTH
:	O
Group	O
of	O
greedy	O
starlings	BISP
feeding	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
#birdfeeding	O
#starlings	BISP
#birds	O
#birding	O
#gardenbirds	O
#wildlife	O
#nature	O
#wi	O
...	O
Rediscovery	O
and	O
Recovery	O
of	O
the	O
Crested	BISP
Ibis	BISP
In	O
the	O
early	TIME
1980s	TIME
,	O
bird	O
conservationists	O
around	O
the	O
world	O
feared	O
tha	O
...	O
https://t.co/Sjyah9s7lj	LINK
Excited	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
latest	O
addition	O
to	O
my	O
#etsy	O
shop	O
:	O
Male	SEX
Northern	BISP
Cardinal	BISP
https://t.co/psESYPd4gk	LINK
#art	O
...	O
https://t.co/9S8phMQeo5	LINK
The	O
Tail-less	O
Chilterns	LOC
Red	BISP
Kite	BISP
in	O
OX10	O
has	O
survived	O
into	O
2018	DATE
-LRB-	O
over	O
a	O
year	O
without	O
a	O
tail	O
-RRB-	O
,	O
but	O
its	O
odd	O
shape	O
see	O
...	O
https://t.co/1lFlr7Mct3	LINK
Robin	BISP
popped	O
in	O
today	O
.	O
#Robin	BISP
#birds	O
#lumber	O
#hardwood	O
#surrey	O
https://t.co/RDL61UGXO3	LINK
Had	O
a	NUMB
pair	NUMB
of	NUMB
bullfinches	BISP
visiting	O
our	O
#Oxfordshire	LOC
garden	O
this	TIME
morning	TIME
.	O
Only	O
an	O
occasional	O
visitor	O
,	O
usually	O
around	O
...	O
https://t.co/m48UhufMK7	LINK
Love	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
air	O
!	O
Flamingo	BISP
Couple	NUMB
clicked	O
by	O
Praveen	PERS
Premkumar	PERS
#SaevusMagazine	O
#SaevusGallery	O
#SaevusWildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/zRbf5OJtBx	LINK
A	O
very	O
obliging	O
heron	BISP
at	O
@YSPsculpture	O
this	TIME
morning	TIME
#bird	O
#wildlifephotography	O
https://t.co/d200hFv0ir	LINK
Oh	O
I	O
do	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
beside	O
the	O
sea	O
...	O
a	O
beaut	O
of	O
a	O
day	O
in	O
#Castlerock	LOC
view	O
of	O
#birds	O
#seagulls	BISP
paddling	O
#Portstewart	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/FHxd4tRK1W	LINK
RT	RTWT
@JonDavatzPhoto	AUTH
:	O
Great	BISP
Blue	BISP
Heron	BISP
Series	O
by	O
@JonDavatzPhoto	O
at	O
@picfair	O
:	O
https://t.co/yqXChGG9Py	LINK
by	O
Jon	PERS
Davatz	PERS
#bird	O
#wildlife	O
#photo	O
A	O
...	O
A	O
very	O
gray	O
morning	O
in	O
#EverettWA	O
The	O
highlight	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
The	O
Pintails	BISP
are	O
back	O
!	O
Spotted	O
on	O
the	O
Everett	LOC
Waterfron	O
...	O
https://t.co/ZaUm1SXxhk	LINK
Spot	O
the	O
red	BISP
whiskered	BISP
bulbul	BISP
on	O
your	O
Coonoor	LOC
trip	O
...	O
#birds	O
#coonoorhomestay	O
#explorenilgiris	O
#coonoordiaries	O
...	O
https://t.co/RN5CgHto1Y	LINK
Here	O
's	O
a	O
beautiful	O
Evening	BISP
Grosbeak	BISP
for	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
.	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/ysY3Is1g9W	LINK
Lovely	O
female	SEX
Northern	BISP
Cardinal	BISP
trying	O
to	O
stay	O
warm	O
this	TIME
cold	O
morning	TIME
in	O
#NC	O
happy	O
#birding	O
#birdwatching	O
...	O
https://t.co/TCMJXF5VWK	LINK
10	NUMB
Hawfinch	BISP
in	O
Darley	LOC
Dale	LOC
at	O
St	LOC
Helen	LOC
's	LOC
at	O
11.40	TIME
SK	O
266	O
629	O
#derbyshire	O
#birding	O
Costa	O
Rican	O
Pygmy-owl	BISP
-LRB-	O
#Glaucidium	BISP
costaricanum	BISP
-RRB-	O
accosted	O
by	O
a	O
hummingbird	BISP
that	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
white-throated	O
mou	O
...	O
https://t.co/3uwdDj4CIY	LINK
RT	RTWT
@BeadXS	ATUH
:	O
Realistic	O
Owl	BISP
Necklace	O
,	O
Hoot	BISP
Owl	BISP
,	O
Gift	O
Idea	O
#owljewelry	O
#bird	O
#holidaygift	O
#Christmas	O
#sterlingsilver	O
https://t.co/17jfk6GnHX…	LINK
RT	RTWT
@OfficialZSL	AUTH
:	O
Happy	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
!	O
This	O
beautiful	O
#bird	O
is	O
a	O
violet-backed	BISP
starling	BISP
,	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
an	O
amethyst	BISP
starling	BISP
,	O
found	O
in	O
sub	O
...	O
Great	BISP
Blue	BISP
Heron	BISP
wade	O
fishing	O
.	O
?	O
#canonfavpic	O
#SaturdayMorning	TIME
#bird	O
#greatblueheron	BISP
#waterbirds	O
#photooftheday	O
...	O
https://t.co/lMxA4R85cz	LINK
How	O
on	O
earth	O
did	O
I	O
miss	O
it	O
.	O
.	O
National	O
bird	O
day	O
was	O
yesterday	TIME
!	O
Flamingos	BISP
and	O
Swan	BISP
are	O
still	O
available	O
...	O
https://t.co/vfFN8VVh3G	LINK
Nicobar	BISP
Pigeon	BISP
Sketches	O
drawn	O
from	O
life	O
at	O
@ARTIS	O
Zoo	O
,	O
Amsterdam	LOC
,	O
with	O
a	O
Parallel	O
calligraphy	O
pen	O
.	O
#traditionalart	O
...	O
https://t.co/6ps1vpdulD	LINK
Pukeko	BISP
bird	O
pillow	O
,	O
new	LOC
zealand	LOC
pillow	O
,	O
nz	O
theme	O
pillow	O
,	O
blue	O
pukeko	BISP
cushion	O
,	O
childrens	O
bird	O
pillow	O
,	O
nz	O
native	O
bird	O
...	O
https://t.co/nQZkw4FDJM	LINK
On	O
January	DATE
20th	DATE
we	O
'll	O
be	O
hosting	O
a	O
potluck	O
dinner	O
and	O
a	O
showing	O
of	O
Saving	O
the	O
Ghost	O
Birds	O
:	O
Whooping	BISP
Cranes	BISP
and	O
the	O
...	O
https://t.co/cT78OgGBLL	LINK
Ever	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
murre	O
?	O
If	O
you	O
love	O
eating	O
#salmon	O
,	O
you	O
show	O
know	O
about	O
this	O
#bird	O
.	O
Happy	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
...	O
https://t.co/zb1rvLKKl9	LINK
Red	BISP
Billed	BISP
Hornbill	BISP
Sketches	O
drawn	O
from	O
life	O
at	O
@ARTIS	O
Zoo	O
,	O
Amsterdam	LOC
,	O
with	O
a	O
Parallel	O
calligraphy	O
pen	O
.	O
...	O
https://t.co/jjOkcv4lP7	LINK
RT	RTTWT
@ByChauvin	AUTH
:	O
Seagulls	BISP
&	O
ducks	BISP
#canonfavpic	O
#SaturdayMorning	O
#bird	O
#Ducks	BISP
#seagulls	BISP
#waterbirds	O
#photooftheday	O
#PictureOfTheDay	O
#NatGeo	ORG
#	O
N	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@Niku477021262	AUTH
:	O
Beautiful	O
robin	BISP
#birds	O
https://t.co/7OwOGZOVvy	LINK
RT	RTWT
@USFWSRefuges	AUTH
:	O
From	O
tiny	O
hummingbirds	BISP
to	O
lumbering	BISP
turkeys	BISP
,	O
America	LOC
's	O
#birds	O
come	O
in	O
amazing	O
array	O
of	O
colors	O
,	O
sizes	O
,	O
shapes	O
and	O
behavior	O
...	O
Bald	BISP
Eagle	BISP
in	TIME
November	TIME
#BaldEagle	BISP
,	O
#Eagle	BISP
,	O
#Bird	O
,	O
#Wildlife	O
,	O
#WildlifePhotography	O
,	O
#iPrimeNature	O
,	O
#ChesapeakeBay	O
,	O
...	O
https://t.co/M1PvN9wrgm	LINK
Whats	O
your	O
favourite	O
Bird	O
?	O
?	O
#survey	O
#dailysurvey	O
#bird	O
birds	O
#birds	O
#pigeons	BISP
#Penguins	BISP
#pens	O
#owl	BISP
#angrybird	O
So	O
I	O
've	O
opened	O
a	O
new	O
restaurant	O
,	O
just	O
need	O
some	O
diners	O
@BBCSpringwatch	O
#birds	O
#feeding	O
#Robin	BISP
#sparrow	BISP
https://t.co/duW9swzyZm	LINK
Snowy	BISP
Owls	BISP
spotting	O
rate	O
so	O
far	O
in	O
2018	DATE
-	O
about	O
1	O
for	O
every	O
1.5	O
hrs	O
of	O
open	O
country	O
driving	O
in	O
#Alberta	LOC
.	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/bunokKcuaP	LINK
RT	RTWT
@Tweets_rw	AUTH
:	O
Turnstone	BISP
demonstrates	O
how	O
to	O
eat	O
periwinkles	O
-	O
Yuck	O
!	O
@RSPBGlasgow	O
#Birds	O
@wildlife_uk	O
https://t.co/IQLKHXxMHQ	LINK
RT	RTWT
@victorthevole	AUTH
:	O
What	O
better	O
reason	O
is	O
there	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
the	O
#camera	O
,	O
than	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
#robin	BISP
#bluetit	BISP
#birds	O
#wildllife	O
@Natures_V	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@MiaLittleWolf	AUTH
:	O
For	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
cheeky	O
#BlueTit	BISP
#Illustration	O
I	O
did	O
a	O
while	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
get	O
to	O
drawing	O
#Birds	O
again	O
!	O
http	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@IBIS_journal	AUTH
:	O
The	O
invisible	O
bird	O
:	O
what	O
makes	O
the	O
#nightjar	BISP
a	O
camouflage	O
https://t.co/nirz3Rc3X9	LINK
#ornithology	O
@CosmosMagazine	ORG
https://t.…	LINK
Mourning	BISP
doves	BISP
in	O
my	O
backyard	O
-LRB-	O
5-20-2017	DATE
-RRB-	O
#birds	O
#doves	O
#NaturePhotography	O
https://t.co/laS65U85MP	LINK
#bluejay	BISP
landing	O
on	O
the	O
#bird	O
feeder	O
https://t.co/zsDYpKi07T	LINK
Hummingbird	BISP
2	O
Gift	O
Tags	O
https://t.co/qI1xbQQWW1	LINK
via	O
@Etsy	O
#naturecuts	O
#etsy	O
#gifttags	O
#hummingbird	BISP
#bird	O
#backyardbirds	O
#nature	O
#momshop	O
Winter	O
#Birding	O
at	O
the	O
frozen	O
#DelawareRiver	LOC
#BaldEagle	BISP
#BurlingtonIsland	LOC
#NJ	LOC
#Photography	O
https://t.co/LstbRPEu2y	LINK
Pelican	BISP
Preening	O
Party	O
A	O
favorite	O
place	O
for	O
the	O
pelicans	BISP
to	O
relax	O
&	O
preen	O
in	O
a	O
social	O
gathering	O
American	O
White	O
Peli	O
...	O
https://t.co/vGOg4DnbFj	LINK
Amazing	O
Winter	O
Cardinal	BISP
bird	O
watching	O
!	O
https://t.co/r6x3QzahiV	LINK
#birding	O
Blue	BISP
Tit	BISP
in	O
Rozelle	LOC
Park	LOC
Ayr	O
.	O
.@ScottishBirding	O
@Natures_Voice	O
@WildlifeMag	O
@BBCSpringwatch	O
@Britnatureguide	O
...	O
https://t.co/tCwPjjKAOa	LINK
@BarnOwlCentre	O
They	O
most	O
certainly	O
are	O
??	O
Here	O
's	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
#Robins	BISP
that	O
live	O
in	O
my	O
#Catford	O
#garden	O
here	O
in	O
#London	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/AMnFfzB43s	LINK
I	O
did	O
n't	O
know	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
job	O
.	O
Awesome	O
!	O
#Science	O
#birds	O
#scicomm	O
https://t.co/1LirZiq9vR	LINK
nice	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
wee	O
flock	O
of	O
snipe	BISP
heading	O
to	O
roost	O
over	O
the	O
reedbed	O
earlier	O
@wildlife_uk	O
@NatureUK	O
#photography	O
...	O
https://t.co/RkKxSPz2ki	LINK
#Hawk	BISP
#Painting	O
#Purple	O
#Blue	O
#Bird	O
Of	O
Prey	O
Wild	O
Desert	O
Animal	O
#Art	O
#Gift	O
For	O
Bird	O
Lover	O
Housewarming	O
...	O
https://t.co/q3OwEsHdOu	LINK
RT	RTWT
@petregister	AUTH
:	O
FOUND	O
Bird	O
Budgie	BISP
in	O
Halifax	LOC
West	LOC
Yorkshire	LOC
https://t.co/4U3gPGQYMW	LINK
#halifax	LOC
#	O
#bird	O
#petregister	O
pls	O
RT	O
RT	RTWT
@MyFrogCroaked	AUTH
:	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
most	O
endangered	O
#birds	O
is	O
the	O
Bali	BISP
Myna	BISP
-LRB-	O
Leucopsar	BISP
rothschildi	BISP
-RRB-	O
.	O
This	O
species	O
nearly	O
vanished	O
due	O
to	O
...	O
``	O
Does	O
my	O
bum	O
look	O
big	O
on	O
this	O
?	O
''	O
Fluffed	O
up	O
Long	BISP
tailed	BISP
tit	BISP
,	O
hunkered	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
hedgerow	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
my	O
images	O
are	O
ava	O
...	O
https://t.co/co3xKo4rzG	LINK
RT	RTWT
@BCsBargainBin	AUTH
:	O
#Hawk	BISP
#Painting	O
#Purple	O
#Blue	O
#Bird	O
Of	O
Prey	O
Wild	O
Desert	O
Animal	O
#Art	O
#Gift	O
For	O
Bird	O
Lover	O
Housewarming	O
https://t.co/VSAmu…	LINK
Female	SEX
Downy	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
visiting	O
the	O
suet	O
feeder	O
.	O
@PFWCanada	O
#nature	O
#birds	O
#winter	O
#cold	O
#Ontario	LOC
https://t.co/QeA3wDUCEV	LINK
Perch	O
#perch	O
#travel	O
##	O
creative	O
#architecture	O
#design	O
#bird	O
#oxford	O
#pigeons	BISP
#house	O
...	O
https://t.co/ddBJAMmweY	LINK
RT	RTWT
@MstagcPhotog	AUTH
:	O
Mockingbird	BISP
#nature	O
#naturephotography	O
#wildlife	O
#wildlifephotography	O
#birds	O
#birdphotography	O
#photography	O
https://t.co/…	LINK
Hi	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
our	O
`	O
Beautiful	O
Owl	BISP
,	O
design	O
on	O
a	O
t-shirt	O
,	O
now	O
available	O
from	O
our	O
Redbubble	O
shop	O
:	O
-RRB-	O
...	O
https://t.co/eRiaQVg7pu	LINK
Blue	BISP
Jay	BISP
#bird	O
#birdphotography	O
#birdstagram	O
#canada	LOC
#nature	O
https://t.co/TQ6oQEfhQ4	LINK
Made	O
a	O
little	O
friend	O
today	O
at	O
#Glynllifon	LOC
#Robin	BISP
#birdsofinstagram	O
#bird	O
#robinredbreast	O
#Wales	O
...	O
https://t.co/CweClqHK6C	LINK
Downy	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
-LRB-	O
Picoides	BISP
pubescens	BISP
-RRB-	O
#DownyWoodpecker	BISP
#Woodpecker	BISP
#DOWO	O
...	O
https://t.co/WqKn6rjetz	LINK
Blue	BISP
Jay	BISP
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
pine	O
Tree	O
#winter	O
#nature	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/DH4Z1PtWqd	LINK
The	O
Barn	BISP
Owl	BISP
,	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
favourite	O
#birds	O
for	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
...@WildUK1	O
@wildlife_uk	O
#birdwatching	O
#wildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/Ojd0aMUC5b	LINK
RT	RTWT
@longvictorian4	AUTH
:	O
The	O
Vain	O
Jackdaw	O
-	O
an	O
illustration	O
by	O
Nora	PERS
Fry	PERS
for	O
Aesop	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
published	O
by	O
J.	PERS
Coker	PERS
-LRB-	O
1920	DATE
-RRB-	O
.	O
#Peacocks	BISP
#birds	O
https	O
...	O
If	O
I	O
was	O
smaller	O
,	O
this	O
osprey	BISP
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
for	O
its	O
next	O
meal	O
.	O
#birding	O
#osprey	BISP
#raptor	O
#wildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/dej5ybJ67n	LINK
Two	O
#Hummingbirds	BISP
in	O
a	O
moment	O
in	O
#WestHollywood	BISP
#California	LOC
.	O
#weho	O
#hummingbird	BISP
#bird	O
#birds	O
#design	O
#graphicdesign	O
...	O
https://t.co/tUi4wKVDAr	LINK
Starting	O
2018	DATE
with	O
Hummingbirds	BISP
in	O
Costa	LOC
Rica	LOC
>	O
Costa	LOC
Rica	LOC
is	O
a	O
fa	O
>>	O
https://t.co/9q5dwrUZYs	LINK
#bird	O
https://t.co/IVNJj9qL4z	LINK
Here	O
's	O
a	O
sweet	O
little	O
Tricolored	BISP
Heron	BISP
for	O
your	O
Saturday	TIME
.	O
??	O
#tricoloredheron	O
#heron	BISP
#bird	O
...	O
https://t.co/bKDaI9NX5s	LINK
RT	RTWT
@SerenaVachon	AUTH
:	O
Cardinal	BISP
in	O
the	O
sunlight	O
#nature	O
#photography	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/wQ5NdkYKsJ	LINK
New	O
#pileatedwoodpecker	BISP
in	O
progress	O
-	O
sepia	O
watercolor	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
©	O
Rebecca	PERS
Latham	PERS
?	O
.	O
#animallovers	O
#wildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/vsRIfhYbgB	LINK
RT	RTWT
@Fromanurbanlake	AUTH
:	O
Robin	BISP
.	O
Just	O
using	O
the	O
fence	O
as	O
a	O
hopping	O
off	O
spot	O
.	O
#robin	BISP
#europeanrobin	BISP
#robinredbreast	BISP
#redbreast	O
#bird	O
#birds	O
#bir	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@DavidGoodmanPix	AUTH
:	O
The	O
Mockingbird	BISP
of	O
West	LOC
23rd	LOC
!	O
.	O
Happy	O
National	O
Bird	O
Day	O
!!!	O
???	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
#Mockingbird	BISP
#Bird	O
#Birds	O
#West	O
...	O
The	O
Cardinals	BISP
are	O
taking	O
advantage	O
of	O
the	O
fresh	O
water	O
too	O
.	O
#cardinals	BISP
#cardinal	BISP
#bird	O
#wildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/eeSrK9gOxF	LINK
Love	O
seeing	O
this	O
guy	O
#redbelliedwoodpecker	BISP
#mybackyard	O
#bird	O
#woodpecker	BISP
#thruruthseyes	O
https://t.co/sCWaOtLOML	LINK
Alvaston	LOC
Lake	LOC
-LRB-	O
SK3734	O
-RRB-	O
2	NUMB
Ring	BISP
Necked	BISP
Parakeet	BISP
#derbyshire	O
#birding	O
Lovely	O
?	O
Amazonas	LOC
,	O
Brazil	LOC
-	O
@alebormida	O
?	O
Use	O
#travelersonearth	O
to	O
get	O
featured	O
!	O
??	O
#parrot	BISP
#bird	O
#brazil	O
#amazonas	O
...	O
https://t.co/QIf7jLT7Ty	LINK
@BBCTwo	O
loving	O
Hugh	O
's	O
wild	O
west	O
and	O
its	O
piece	O
on	O
#dippers	BISP
#ornithology	O
RT	RTWT
@QuartoExplores	AUTH
:	O
#NationalBirdDay	O
,	O
they	O
say	O
?	O
OK	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
're	O
a	O
little	O
obsessed	O
...	O
#birds	O
#ornithology	O
#Owls	BISP
#Hummingbirds	BISP
#hummingbird	BISP
#bir	O
...	O
Food	O
getting	O
scarce	O
for	O
wildlife	O
.	O
Keep	O
an	O
eye	O
on	O
your	O
pets	O
.	O
Little	O
dog	O
snatched	O
by	O
hungry	O
eagle	BISP
and	O
amazingly	O
survi	O
...	O
https://t.co/PqiDnxSRpy	LINK
Sunbird	BISP
!!	O
#spotted	O
#bird	O
#birds	O
#birdphotography	O
#BirdsOfAFeather	O
#nature	O
#naturephotography	O
#photography	O
#PHOTO	O
...	O
https://t.co/yAz06AyXvi	LINK
Spotted	BISP
Dove	BISP
!!	O
#spotted	O
#bird	O
#birds	O
#birdphotography	O
#BirdsOfAFeather	O
#nature	O
#naturephotography	O
#photography	O
...	O
https://t.co/R3dG8ZjU6g	LINK
Young	O
eaglet	BISP
looking	O
down	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
#eagle	BISP
#bird	O
#bestbirdshots	O
#birdsofprey	O
#sault	O
@	O
Sault	LOC
Sainte	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/NzqP8h83qi	LINK
Northern	BISP
#mockingbird	BISP
#bird	O
#birdsofinstagram	O
?	O
#winter	O
Let	O
's	O
go	O
#Hiking	O
!	O
#OptOutside	O
and	O
enjoy	O
...	O
https://t.co/CvdeRS7M1q	LINK
A	O
very	O
Fox	BISP
Sparrow-full	BISP
morning	O
in	O
@GreenWoodHF	O
:	O
https://t.co/IXJ2EXYsaz	LINK
#UrbanBirding	O
#Birding	O
#Brooklyn	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/PLV5Y3OdqW	LINK
Thanks	O
for	O
the	O
paint	O
job	O
guys	O
!	O
#gråsiska	O
#redpoll	BISP
#bird	O
#nature	O
#naturelovers	O
#naturephotography	O
#wildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/loYfyRatxu	LINK
A	O
familiar	O
face	O
with	O
a	O
novel	O
behavior	O
raises	O
challenges	O
for	O
conservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hooded	BISP
Grebe	BISP
;	O
American	O
Mink	O
in	O
ari	O
...	O
https://t.co/JRR6nhgfAF	LINK
The	O
parakeet	O
protectors	O
:	O
Understanding	O
opposition	O
to	O
introduced	O
species	O
management	O
of	O
Monk	BISP
Parakeet	BISP
-LRB-	O
Myiopsitta	BISP
mon	BISP
...	O
https://t.co/kUaxqifmZq	LINK
RT	RTWT
@newblogologist	AUTH
:	O
African	BISP
Fish	BISP
Eagle	BISP
surveying	O
the	O
dam	O
for	O
its	O
next	O
meal	O
#zimbabwe	LOC
#WildLowveld	O
#birds	O
#eagle	BISP
#africa	LOC
#Nature	O
#wildlife	O
#	O
...	O
Thought-provoking	O
image	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
#tpiotd	O
#art	O
#modernart	O
#surreal	O
#dream	O
#nightmare	O
#owl	BISP
#owls	BISP
#justice	O
#judgment	O
...	O
https://t.co/o436sTZxrP	LINK
Your	O
pet	O
could	O
be	O
a	O
star-we	O
need	O
honorees	O
-	O
#birds	O
-	O
#parrot	BISP
or	O
#chicken	O
or	O
#duck	O
-	O
#mice	O
#ponies	O
#bunnies	O
#gerbils	O
...	O
https://t.co/aES2oeDegm	LINK
Titmouse	BISP
!	O
#bird	O
#birdwatching	O
#birds	O
#birding	O
#titmouse	BISP
#stukulsguidetobirds	O
https://t.co/4zm4LZ8FFH	LINK
RT	RTWT
@Rachllea	AUTH
:	O
A	O
Little	O
Chickadee	BISP
-	O
https://t.co/5Vs0AEJ4gm	LINK
#wildlifephotography	O
#nature	O
#bird	O
https://t.co/6iqUgbq3w6	LINK
Carolina	BISP
#chickadee	BISP
#bird	O
#birdsofinstagram	O
?	O
#winter	O
Let	O
's	O
go	O
#Hiking	O
!	O
#OptOutside	O
and	O
enjoy	O
...	O
https://t.co/qRpVBRY5fe	LINK
RT	RTWT
@OrnellaBonomini	AUTH
:	O
DOWNLOAD	O
THIS	O
PHOTO	O
AT	O
LINK	O
https://t.co/8S3AaCBKVc	LINK
#seagull	BISP
#GullsLive	O
#gull	BISP
#bird	O
#birds	O
#wildlife	O
#animal	O
#animals	O
...	O
Hawk	BISP
.	O
#bird	O
#birds	O
#nature	O
#birdphotography	O
#wildlife	O
#wildlifephotography	O
#birdsofinstagram	O
#animal	O
#naturalbeauty	O
...	O
https://t.co/ykXtsmwYMz	LINK
Crazy	O
color	O
#bird	O
#finches	BISP
@	O
The	O
Bird	O
Shop	O
https://t.co/7n2IihirB9	LINK
Spotted	O
this	O
#toucan	BISP
#bird	O
in	O
#costarica	LOC
?	O
@	O
Vandara	ORG
Hot	ORG
Springs	ORG
&	O
Adventure	ORG
https://t.co/OE8FXgiHaW	LINK
I	O
wish	O
I	O
knew	O
more	O
about	O
#birds	O
but	O
these	O
guys	O
have	O
been	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
#birdfeeder	O
all	O
winter	O
,	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
sparrow	BISP
wit	O
...	O
https://t.co/EiYhxsvWF0	LINK
RT	RTWT
@bettyjo62	AUTH
:	O
A	O
Gull	BISP
taken	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
dull	O
day	O
#birds	O
#Portmeadow	LOC
#Oxfordshire	LOC
https://t.co/9jvA8WOK8h	LINK
RT	BISP
@KarpanParkland	BISP
:	O
Sparkling	BISP
violetear	BISP
hummingbird	BISP
,	O
Mindo	LOC
#Ecuador	LOC
#AllYouNeedIsEcuador	O
#birding	O
#birdphotography	O
#naturephotography	O
#wild	O
...	O
Fiercely	O
vibrant	O
colours	O
are	O
the	O
peacock	BISP
's	O
trademark	O
-	O
Breathtaking	O
natural	O
beauty	O
personified	O
!	O
-	O
shared	O
with	O
...	O
https://t.co/p8sDGxYzs6	LINK
One	O
of	O
countless	O
many	O
#roughwingedswallow	O
#swallow	BISP
#bird	O
#migratory	O
#snowbird	O
#overwintering	O
...	O
https://t.co/7MJtYvUSxf	LINK
Brown	O
winter	O
woodpecker	BISP
https://t.co/DYVoDCM9pP	LINK
?	O
Wild	O
#Birds	O
Unlimited	O
#birdwatching	O
#gardening	O
#nature	O
...	O
https://t.co/ziU9xgIiaZ	LINK
Bird	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
:	O
Snowflake	BISP
Birds	BISP
https://t.co/snA4TB0Dxt	LINK
?	O
Wild	O
#Birds	O
Unlimited	O
#birdwatching	O
#gardening	O
#nature	O
...	O
https://t.co/xt1aCbwRNH	LINK
a	O
welcome	O
to	O
sunday	O
swallow	BISP
.	O
@Queensland	LOC
#bird	O
#swallow	BISP
#Queensland	LOC
#visitmoretonbayregion	O
#nature	O
#feathers	O
...	O
https://t.co/rIqAuc5JDj	LINK
Progress	O
of	O
a	O
cover	O
up	O
from	O
today	O
.	O
#bird	O
#hummingbird	BISP
#colortattoo	O
#eternalink	O
#realism	O
...	O
https://t.co/FMsbl4ySUK	LINK
RT	RTWT
@iaindwelch	AUTH
:	O
Good	O
night	O
,	O
lovely	O
folks	O
!!	O
#bird	O
#watercolour	O
#nuthatch	nuthatch
#nature	O
https://t.co/aKrP3hpvbq	LINK
Male	SEX
downy	BISP
woodpecker	BISP
in	O
the	O
plum	O
tree	O
Sat	O
.	O
aft.	O
,	O
SE	O
GA.	O
#birding	O
#birds	O
#bird	O
#nature	O
#NaturePhotography	O
...	O
https://t.co/5W96SaOqkJ	LINK
Duffy	O
https://t.co/U70Hx5ceui	LINK
via	O
@redbubble	O
#CanadaGoose	BISP
#gosling	O
#goose	BISP
#bird	O
#birds	O
#animal	O
#animals	O
#wildlife	O
RT	RTWT
@guyedwardes	AUTH
:	O
Snowy	BISP
owl	BISP
-LRB-	O
Bubo	BISP
scandiacus	BISP
-RRB-	O
taken	O
yesterday	TIME
in	O
Ontario	LOC
,	O
Canada	LOC
just	TIME
after	TIME
dawn	TIME
.	O
©	O
Guy	PERS
Edwardes	PERS
Photography	O
#birds	O
#birdw	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@FisherSpeaks	AUTH
:	O
Snowy	BISP
Owls	BISP
spotting	O
rate	O
so	O
far	O
in	O
2018	DATE
-	O
about	O
1	O
for	O
every	O
1.5	O
hrs	O
of	O
open	O
country	O
driving	O
in	O
#Alberta	LOC
.	O
#birds	O
https://t…	LINK
Crow	BISP
in	O
Cowboy	O
Boots	O
.	O
#western	O
#humor	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/jA0oDbeWAL	LINK
RT	RTWT
@DrDylanParry	AUTH
:	O
#Bullfinch	BISP
eating	O
lunch	O
in	O
our	O
garden	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
watch	O
this	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/yJ3gHbofAu	LINK
We	O
are	O
officially	O
off	O
to	O
track	O
down	O
a	O
snowy	BISP
owl	BISP
!	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/4OPkTs57LD	LINK
hawk	BISP
https://t.co/xeidAIw38j	LINK
#birds	O
#animals	O
RT	RTWT
@CatherineSher10	AUTH
:	O
A	O
male	SEX
cardinal	BISP
braves	O
a	O
snowstorm	O
,	O
perched	O
on	O
a	O
branch	O
#bird	O
#ArtForSale	O
#Snow	BISP
#Snowy	BISP
#winter	O
#CLS	O
https://t.co/zod…	LINK
Mute	BISP
#Swan	BISP
at	O
#HuntingtonBeach	O
Central	LOC
Park	LOC
,	O
Huntington	LOC
Beach	LOC
,	O
#OrangeCounty	LOC
,	O
#California	LOC
,	O
USA	LOC
.	O
#nature	O
#wildlife	O
...	O
https://t.co/KQYQi4hpcF	LINK
RT	RTWT
@Coffeewarblers	AUTH
:	O
My	O
bird	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
often	O
hear	O
the	O
thin	O
call	O
of	O
Goldcrests	BISP
on	O
my	O
daily	O
walk	O
.	O
https://t.co/9N8wtNFthL	LINK
#birds	O
#nature	O
@	O
...	O
Hairy	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
.	O
#birds	O
#nature	O
#nofilter	O
https://t.co/p7edvJuAb8	LINK
https://t.co/DPXAFr3wlx	LINK
It	O
's	O
still	O
too	O
orangey	O
for	O
crows	BISP
.	O
#crow	BISP
#bird	O
#birdsofinstagram	O
https://t.co/nST2ZZeKHq	LINK
Great-spotted	BISP
Woodpecker	BISP
,	O
South	LOC
Devon	LOC
@DevonWildlife	O
@simbirds	O
@RSPB	O
@NatureUK	O
@Britnatureguide	O
#garden	O
#birds	O
...	O
https://t.co/cB41Smz5Yz	LINK
RT	RTWT
@jammyjimm	AUTH
:	O
Spotted	BISP
Redshank	BISP
#birding	O
https://t.co/cO6oDe2ruy	LINK
Spotted	BISP
Redshank	BISP
#birding	O
https://t.co/cO6oDe2ruy	LINK
Purple	BISP
Sandpiper	BISP
at	O
rest	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
dispute	O
over	O
the	O
best	O
feeding	O
spot	O
#birding	O
#Norfolk	LOC
https://t.co/x4EgCpII4r	LINK
When	O
the	O
lighting	O
hits	O
just	O
so	O
#northerncardinal	BISP
#cardinal	BISP
#female	SEX
#bird	O
#passerine	O
#instabird	O
...	O
https://t.co/xjctXvK3sX	LINK
Nice	O
views	O
of	O
Purple-gaped	BISP
Honeyeater	BISP
from	O
my	O
@BirdingEcotours	O
Western	LOC
Australia	LOC
tour	O
in	TIME
December	TIME
#wildoz	O
#birding	O
...	O
https://t.co/iG4BvyDbwt	LINK
Red-tailed	BISP
hawk	BISP
this	TIME
afternoon	TIME
.	O
Nothing	O
like	O
a	O
cold	O
,	O
clear	O
winter	O
sky	O
as	O
a	O
background	O
.	O
#birds	O
#birding	O
1/2	O
https://t.co/mrXzulpvGl	LINK
#bird	O
#acornwoodpecker	BISP
#wildlife	O
#wildlifephotography	O
#maderacanyon	LOC
#nature	O
#naturephotography	O
A	O
photo	O
of	O
an	O
Acorn	O
...	O
https://t.co/YAPJhDP39e	LINK
Mourning	BISP
Dove	BISP
:	O
A	O
symbol	O
of	O
affection	O
and	O
peace	O
.	O
#MourningDove	BISP
#dove	BISP
#bird	O
#backyardbird	O
#birding	O
#peace	O
https://t.co/DTxpvjWQTB	LINK
Double	O
breasted	O
commorant	BISP
.	O
#seabird	O
#audobon	O
#illustration	O
#draw	O
#bird	O
#birder	O
#love	O
https://t.co/e2Jl6jhHSv	LINK
Northern	BISP
Mockingbird	BISP
.	O
#bird	O
#photo	O
https://t.co/qZ4hqHh14D	LINK
RT	RTWT
@eopman	AUTH
:	O
Morning	TIME
drawing	O
2	O
#drawing	O
#sketch	O
#painting	O
#art	O
#draw365	O
#artist	O
#Twitart	O
#followart	O
#birds	O
#duck	BISP
https://t.co/eMn6b8Eg7d	LINK
Great	BISP
Reed	BISP
Warblers	BISP
may	O
benefit	O
from	O
improved	O
conditions	O
after	O
intra-tropical	O
movement	O
compared	O
to	O
the	O
conditions	O
...	O
https://t.co/1OaCVuBR7V	LINK
Confirmed	O
-	O
Bullfinches	BISP
stick	O
together	O
for	O
years	O
,	O
#ornithology	O
news	O
via	O
@RareBirdAlertUK	O
https://t.co/o1zVu2lMjz	LINK
#RedTailedHawk	BISP
-LRB-	O
#ButeoJamaicensis	BISP
-RRB-	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
#Winter	O
#hunt	O
over	O
#CentralPark	LOC
#HarlemMeer	LOC
#NYC	LOC
#NewYork	LOC
.	O
#flickr	O
...	O
https://t.co/wleEiAFwSC	LINK
Great	BISP
Egret	BISP
in	O
ditch	O
Hesketh	LOC
Out	LOC
Marsh	LOC
east	O
and	O
Am/Euro	O
Wigeon	BISP
hybrid	O
-LRB-	O
chestnut	O
hue	O
to	O
cheeks	O
,	O
warm	O
orange	O
crown	O
-RRB-	O
o	O
...	O
https://t.co/WfbzO8bzVC	LINK
RT	RTWT
@grasstraximage	AUTH
:	O
Singing	O
Blue	BISP
Tit	BISP
@rspbconwy	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
@Natures_Voice	O
@BirdWatchingMag	O
@nwalestweetsuk	O
#birds	O
#wildlifephotography	O
h	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@ParrotsGroup	AUTH
:	O
2017	DATE
:	O
an	O
important	O
year	O
for	O
#Africa	LOC
's	O
wild	O
grey	BISP
&	O
timneh	BISP
parrots	BISP
#parrots	BISP
#conservation	O
#parrotsci	O
#ornithology	O
https	O
:	O
/	O
/	O
...	O
Crowned	BISP
#Eagle	BISP
in	O
iSimangaliso	LOC
Wetland	LOC
Park	LOC
#IBA	O
#StLucia	LOC
#SouthAfrica	LOC
-	O
not	O
all	O
of	O
our	O
#research	O
breeding	O
pairs	O
ar	O
...	O
https://t.co/V8oLLA7VbA	LINK
Diurnal	O
and	O
Nocturnal	O
Dive	O
Durations	O
and	O
Inter-Dive	O
Intervals	O
of	O
Stiff-Tailed	BISP
Ducks	BISP
in	O
Puerto	LOC
Rico	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/L2c3TblqiG	LINK
Lone	O
Tricolored	BISP
Heron	BISP
making	O
his	O
way	O
through	O
reeds	O
at	O
Ritch	LOC
Grissom	LOC
Memorial	LOC
Wetlands	LOC
https://t.co/5rLnQe2q7v	LINK
#birds	O
https://t.co/XWkDk58pZR	LINK
Art	O
Print	O
Red	BISP
Cardinal	BISP
bird	O
art	O
watercolor	O
painting	O
https://t.co/GCMkuw02JV	LINK
via	O
@Etsy	O
#Cardinal	BISP
#red	O
#birds	O
#art	O
...	O
https://t.co/9wpP2Xhdyy	LINK
Steely-Vented	BISP
Hummingbird	BISP
Quindio	LOC
Colombia	LOC
/	O
This	O
photo	O
was	O
taken	O
June	DATE
16	DATE
,	DATE
2017	DATE
,	O
in	O
Calarca	LOC
,	O
Colombia	LOC
.	O
/	O
©	O
2017	DATE
Adam	PERS
...	O
https://t.co/I8KDbaEuOg	LINK
RT	RTWT
@GoTrails	AUTH
:	O
Swarming	O
#birds	O
over	O
#Lake	LOC
Lucerne	LOC
,	O
Switzerland	LOC
#travel	O
#birding	O
#gotrails	O
#outdoors	O
#TTOT	O
https://t.co/TIR4FFcL43	LINK
https://t…	LINK
The	O
mega	O
Scarlet-banded	BISP
Barbet	BISP
from	O
the	O
@zootherabirding	O
Northern	LOC
Peru	LOC
tour	O
.	O
See	O
https://t.co/UKbv7eLtI4	LINK
for	O
more	O
i	O
...	O
https://t.co/fI902AJEaz	LINK
#MondayBirdDay	O
-	O
The	O
beautifully	O
marked	O
Red-crested	BISP
Korhaan	BISP
-	O
Kruger	LOC
National	LOC
Park	LOC
.	O
Spotted	O
on	O
safari	O
with	O
Outdoor	O
...	O
https://t.co/FWV0tFEchb	LINK
Goldfinches	BISP
back	O
on	O
the	O
niger/nyjer	O
seed	O
today	O
.	O
#birding	O
#Lincolnshire	O
RT	RTWT
@amolalolo21	AUTH
:	O
#pair	NUMB
of	NUMB
parrots	BISP
...	O
#birds	O
#naturelovers	O
#NaturePhotography	O
#Lovely	O
#Beatiful	O
#colors	O
#colorful	O
https://t.co/nGczZlNJkY	LINK
RT	RTWT
@mido3bitte	AUTH
:	O
Japanese	BISP
White-Eye	BISP
#birds	O
#wildlife	O
23.12.2017	DATE
https://t.co/TES3U935Oj	LINK
For	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
yesterday	TIME
I	O
got	O
close	O
enough	O
to	O
some	O
male	SEX
surf	BISP
scoters	BISP
to	O
really	O
see	O
them	O
in	O
detail	O
-LRB-	O
...	O
https://t.co/fx99t290sd	LINK
RT	RTWT
@HikeOurPlanet	O
:	O
Migration	O
:	O
Juvenile	O
Blue-Headed	BISP
Vireo	BISP
https://t.co/ejR6pezhEM	LINK
https://t.co/IQrUUiWdRL	LINK
#birding	O
#birds	O
#nature	O
#photograp	O
...	O
#Hummingbird	BISP
in	O
my	O
wintry	O
sparkling	O
back	O
yard	O
.	O
@TourismAbby	O
@thefraservalley	O
@FraserVN	O
@WildBirdsUnlmtd	O
...	O
https://t.co/TA0CdUFRn3	LINK
RT	RTWT
@ZahranCR	AUTH
:	O
Smallest	O
owl	BISP
of	O
Asia	LOC
?	O
#Bird	O
name	O
:	O
Collared	BISP
owlet	BISP
6	O
inches	O
in	O
size	O
,	O
makes	O
it	O
the	O
smallest	O
owl	BISP
of	O
#BeautifulPakistan	O
??	O
an	O
...	O
#BorealBirdOfTheWeek	O
:	O
Fox	BISP
Sparrow	BISP
!	O
Known	O
for	O
its	O
coppery	O
streaks	O
and	O
splotches	O
,	O
58	O
%	O
of	O
these	O
#birds	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
...	O
https://t.co/w04M7J3rmT	LINK
Status	O
and	O
reproductive	O
outcome	O
of	O
the	O
breeding	O
population	O
of	O
Striated	BISP
Caracaras	BISP
-LRB-	O
Phalcoboenus	BISP
australis	BISP
-RRB-	O
at	O
Frankl	O
...	O
https://t.co/vTmLDQAhLJ	LINK
Snapped	O
this	O
little	O
creature	O
braving	O
the	O
rain	O
today	O
in	O
#Bristol	LOC
.	O
#earthcapture	O
#bird	O
#robin	BISP
https://t.co/JfzGr5oj5s	LINK
RT	RTWT
@eddieledbetter	AUTH
:	O
Red-bellied	BISP
woodpecker	BISP
on	O
a	O
plum	O
tree	O
branch	O
Sun	O
.	O
aft	O
.	O
#birding	O
#birds	O
#bird	O
#NaturePhotography	O
#wildlifephotography	O
#	O
n	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@	AUTH
4KariFoto	AUTH
:	O
Woodpecker	BISP
eating	O
some	O
grub	O
#KariFoto	O
#DailyBird	O
#NV	O
#Canon	O
#photo	O
#Wildlife	O
#birding	O
...	O
https://t.co/sTc5Xa6URk	LINK
RT	RTWT
@AjitaKad	AUTH
:	O
Spotted	O
in	O
in	O
Colombo	LOC
5	O
today	O
.	O
An	O
Indian	BISP
Pond	BISP
Heron	BISP
-	O
in	O
the	O
heart	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
!	O
#lka	O
#birding	O
https://t.co/3FkQFYj616	LINK
#	O
1st	O
attempt	O
at	O
a	O
#Robin	BISP
#Selfie	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
quite	O
a	O
challenge	O
,	O
especially	O
when	O
he	O
landed	O
on	O
my	O
#mobile	O
instead	O
of	O
my	O
s	O
...	O
https://t.co/d9eeOMif1l	LINK
RT	RTWT
@bettyjo62	AUTH
:	O
Our	O
first	O
Hawfinch	BISP
this	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
shot	O
#birds	O
#Oxfordshire	LOC
https://t.co/YyYWLKIw0X	LINK
Critically-endangered	O
Spoon-billed	BISP
Sandpiper	BISP
spotted	O
in	O
Barangay	LOC
Tipsok	LOC
Negros	LOC
Occidental	LOC
https://t.co/IT61Ps0jTf…	LINK
https://t.co/6gZAz33G4y	LINK
RT	RTWT
@JamesSLees	AUTH
:	O
A	O
new	O
one	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
drake	O
Barrow	BISP
's	O
x	O
Common	BISP
Goldeneye	BISP
hybrid	O
on	O
Lake	LOC
Ontario	LOC
#birds	O
#birding	O
#hybrids	O
#wildfowl	BISP
@BirdStudie	O
...	O
Do	O
American	BISP
Golden-Plovers	BISP
-LRB-	O
Pluvialis	BISP
dominica	BISP
-RRB-	O
avoid	O
wind-energy	O
turbines	O
in	O
agricultural	O
fields	O
in	O
Indiana	LOC
during	O
...	O
https://t.co/eHvCJYObTS	LINK
Natal	O
philopatry	O
and	O
juvenile	O
survival	O
in	O
Swainson	BISP
's	BISP
Warblers	BISP
-LRB-	O
Limnothlypis	BISP
swainsonii	BISP
-RRB-	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/twEhakaiTM	LINK
RT	RTWT
@spurdy33	AUTH
:	O
Bald	BISP
Eagle	BISP
in	O
the	O
Mist	LOC
https://t.co/rcFL6JLalO	LINK
#birds	O
#photography	O
RT	RTWT
@RareBirdAlertUK	AUTH
:	O
New	O
species	O
to	O
science	O
-	O
Cordillera	BISP
Azul	BISP
Antbird	BISP
discovered	O
in	O
#Peru	LOC
,	O
#Ornithology	O
https://t.co/sLnKLD4ASK	LINK
https://t.c…	LINK
Seagulls	BISP
dumpster	O
dive	O
at	O
HS	O
Lordships	O
at	O
the	O
Berkeley	LOC
Marina	LOC
,	O
December	DATE
2017	DATE
•	O
•	O
•	O
•	O
•	O
#bird	O
...	O
https://t.co/ApjASoA8Cn	LINK
Flushing	O
responses	O
of	O
Golden	BISP
Eagles	BISP
-LRB-	O
Aquila	BISP
chrysaetos	BISP
-RRB-	O
in	O
response	O
to	O
recreation	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/KnuUHpIdeo	LINK
RT	RTWT
@Elidanza	AUTH
:	O
Still	O
love	O
an	O
owl	BISP
Happy	O
Friday	O
x	O
#watercolour	O
#owl	BISP
#birds	O
#wildlife	O
#animalportrait	O
#BigArtBoost	O
#thedailysketch	O
#movement	O
#	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@BirdTea	AUTH
:	O
Hiding	O
@NatureUK	O
#Robin	BISP
#Bird	O
https://t.co/ZTjbd1hCAO	LINK
Nesting	O
biology	O
of	O
Schiffornis	BISP
stenorhyncha	BISP
-LRB-	O
Tityridae	BISP
-RRB-	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/4z3SUoFK6G	LINK
Red	BISP
robin	BISP
@stefanholmPHOTO	O
#photography	O
#	O
500px	O
#robin	BISP
#bird	O
https://t.co/xU5v1jtCe5	LINK
https://t.co/ORb8cOP93T	LINK
Nesting	O
biology	O
of	O
the	O
Black-throated	BISP
Tody-Tyrant	BISP
-LRB-	O
Hemitriccus	BISP
granadensis	BISP
-RRB-	O
with	O
notes	O
on	O
mating	O
displays	O
...	O
https://t.co/1NVRCKGswV	LINK
Goldfinches	BISP
.	O
#goldfinches	BISP
#birds	O
#photo	O
#photography	O
https://t.co/N68jvnSGAQ	LINK
#Osprey	BISP
in	O
flight	O
carrying	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
fish	O
in	O
TM	O
Goodwin	LOC
WMA	LOC
#Florida	LOC
https://t.co/arFghe8sHf	LINK
#birds	O
https://t.co/N3bwENZZOt	LINK
Love	O
love	O
love	O
this	O
!!	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
snow	O
to	O
feed	O
the	O
cardinals	BISP
in	O
our	O
yard	O
this	O
morning	O
!	O
?	O
-LRB-	O
It	O
's	O
normal	O
to	O
si	O
...	O
https://t.co/5OrPgaxvpG	LINK
RT	RTWT
@emm33	AUTH
:	O
Really	O
cold	O
day	O
yesterday	O
@Natures_Voice	O
Pulbrough	O
Brooks	O
but	O
worth	O
it	O
for	O
our	O
first	O
sighting	O
of	O
Bullfinches	BISP
#birds	O
Reproductive	O
biology	O
of	O
the	O
Tawny-crowned	BISP
Tunchiornis	BISP
-LRB-	O
Tunchiornis	BISP
ochraceiceps	BISP
-RRB-	O
in	O
southern	LOC
Manu	LOC
National	LOC
Park	LOC
,	O
Pe	LOC
...	O
https://t.co/jNN2bNhxkc	LINK
Nice	O
review	O
of	O
a	O
must-have	O
book	O
for	O
gull	BISP
enthusiasts	O
,	O
Malling	PERS
Olsens	PERS
latest	O
:	O
https://t.co/T6XY8hXMTI	LINK
#laridaerule	O
#ornithology	O
#birding	O
The	O
Strange	O
Origin	O
of	O
a	O
Manakin	BISP
's	BISP
Golden	BISP
Crown	O
via	O
@NYTimes	O
#evolution	O
#birds	O
https://t.co/Cww1hZc8Ch	LINK
First	O
breeding	O
record	O
of	O
Zeledon	BISP
's	BISP
Antbird	BISP
-LRB-	O
Hafferia	BISP
zeledoni	BISP
-RRB-	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/4TelNlVb29	LINK
RT	RTWT
@CathySavels	AUTH
:	O
Titmouse	BISP
Bird	O
Print	O
Gray	O
and	O
White	O
https://t.co/LCy718RKuv	LINK
#birds	O
#wildlife	O
#fineart	O
https://t.co/nDvtN0Zwc9	LINK
RT	RTWT
@ZahranCR	AUTH
:	O
Smallest	O
owl	BISP
of	O
Asia	LOC
?	O
#Bird	O
name	O
:	O
Collared	BISP
owlet	BISP
6	O
inches	O
in	O
size	O
,	O
makes	O
it	O
the	O
smallest	O
owl	BISP
of	O
#BeautifulPakistan	O
??	O
an	O
...	O
RT	RTWT
@BenjaminBASSO	AUTH
:	O
Cockatoo	BISP
doodle	O
.	O
#dailydoodle	O
#sketch	O
#illustration	O
#cockatoo	BISP
#artoftheday	O
#ink	O
#inking	O
#bird	O
https://t.co/VEipwlezRS	LINK
Looking	O
forward	O
#bird	O
#nature	O
https://t.co/Pk1gIJKpo2	LINK
https://t.co/bujcifGXIf	LINK
RT	RTWT
@RareBirdAlertUK	AUTH
:	O
Confirmed	O
-	O
Bullfinches	BISP
stick	O
together	O
for	O
years	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/QgTpGsR6sS	LINK
https://t.co/llYlKxZkTH	LINK
The	O
critically	O
endangered	O
and	O
endemic	O
Araripe	BISP
Manakin	BISP
-LRB-	O
Antilophia	BISP
bokermanni	BISP
-RRB-	O
:	O
dietary	O
assessment	O
for	O
conservation	O
...	O
https://t.co/VGUp1HoIUR	LINK
RT	RTWT
@RareBirdAlertUK	AUTH
:	O
Confirmed	O
-	O
Bullfinches	BISP
stick	O
together	O
for	O
years	O
#ornithology	O
https://t.co/QgTpGsR6sS	LINK
https://t.co/llYlKxZkTH	LINK
